,Chapter ID,Place ID,Character ID,Dialogue,tokens,Character Name,Gender,House,pos_tags,entities_people,all_entities_nltk,all_entities_spacy,chunks
0,1,8,4,I should have known that you would be here...Professor McGonagall.,"['known', 'would', '...', 'Professor', 'McGonagall']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('known', 'VBN'), ('would', 'MD'), ('...', ':'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('McGonagall', 'NNP')]",[],[],[McGonagall],(S known/VBN would/MD .../: Professor/NNP McGonagall/NNP)
1,1,8,7,"Good evening, Professor Dumbledore. Are the rumours true, Albus?","['Good', 'evening', 'Professor', 'Dumbledore', 'rumours', 'true', 'Albus']",Minerva McGonagall,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Good', 'JJ'), ('evening', 'NN'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP'), ('rumours', 'VBZ'), ('true', 'JJ'), ('Albus', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Good', 'JJ')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP')])]","[evening, Dumbledore, Albus]","(S
  (GPE Good/JJ)
  evening/NN
  Professor/NNP
  Dumbledore/NNP
  rumours/VBZ
  true/JJ
  (PERSON Albus/NNP))"
2,1,8,4,"I'm afraid so, Professor. The good, and the bad.","[""'m"", 'afraid', 'Professor', 'good', 'bad']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'m"", 'VBP'), ('afraid', 'JJ'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('good', 'JJ'), ('bad', 'JJ')]",[],[],[],(S 'm/VBP afraid/JJ Professor/NNP good/JJ bad/JJ)
3,1,8,7,And the boy?,['boy'],Minerva McGonagall,Female,Gryffindor,"[('boy', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S boy/NN)
4,1,8,4,Hagrid is bringing him.,"['Hagrid', 'bringing']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('bringing', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],(S (GPE Hagrid/NNP) bringing/NN)
5,1,8,7,Do you think it wise to trust Hagrid with something as important as this?,"['think', 'wise', 'trust', 'Hagrid', 'something', 'important']",Minerva McGonagall,Female,Gryffindor,"[('think', 'NN'), ('wise', 'NN'), ('trust', 'NN'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('something', 'NN'), ('important', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],"(S
  think/NN
  wise/NN
  trust/NN
  (PERSON Hagrid/NNP)
  something/NN
  important/JJ)"
6,1,8,4,"Ah, Professor, I would trust Hagrid with my life.","['Ah', 'Professor', 'would', 'trust', 'Hagrid', 'life']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Ah', 'NNP'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('would', 'MD'), ('trust', 'VB'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('life', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],(S Ah/NNP Professor/NNP would/MD trust/VB (GPE Hagrid/NNP) life/NN)
7,1,8,5,"Professor Dumbledore, Sir. Professor McGonagall.","['Professor', 'Dumbledore', 'Sir', 'Professor', 'McGonagall']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Professor', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP'), ('Sir', 'NNP'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('McGonagall', 'NNP')]",[],[],"[Dumbledore, McGonagall]",(S Professor/NNP Dumbledore/NNP Sir/NNP Professor/NNP McGonagall/NNP)
8,1,8,4,"No problems, I trust, Hagrid?","['problems', 'trust', 'Hagrid']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('problems', 'NNS'), ('trust', 'VBP'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],(S problems/NNS trust/VBP (PERSON Hagrid/NNP))
9,1,8,5,"No, sir. Little tyke fell asleep just as we were flying over Bristol. Heh. Try not to wake him. There you go.","['sir', 'Little', 'tyke', 'fell', 'asleep', 'flying', 'Bristol', 'Heh', 'Try', 'wake', 'go']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('sir', 'JJ'), ('Little', 'NNP'), ('tyke', 'NN'), ('fell', 'VBD'), ('asleep', 'RB'), ('flying', 'VBG'), ('Bristol', 'NNP'), ('Heh', 'NNP'), ('Try', 'NNP'), ('wake', 'NN'), ('go', 'VB')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Bristol', 'NNP'), ('Heh', 'NNP'), ('Try', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Bristol', 'NNP'), ('Heh', 'NNP'), ('Try', 'NNP')])]",[Bristol.],"(S
  sir/JJ
  Little/NNP
  tyke/NN
  fell/VBD
  asleep/RB
  flying/VBG
  (PERSON Bristol/NNP Heh/NNP Try/NNP)
  wake/NN
  go/VB)"
10,1,8,7,"Albus, do you really think it's safe, leaving him with these people? I've watched them all day. They're the worst sort of Muggles imaginable. They really are...","['Albus', 'really', 'think', ""'s"", 'safe', 'leaving', 'people', ""'ve"", 'watched', 'day', ""'re"", 'worst', 'sort', 'Muggles', 'imaginable', 'really', '...']",Minerva McGonagall,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Albus', 'NNP'), ('really', 'RB'), ('think', 'VBP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('safe', 'JJ'), ('leaving', 'VBG'), ('people', 'NNS'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('watched', 'VBN'), ('day', 'NN'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('worst', 'JJS'), ('sort', 'NN'), ('Muggles', 'NNP'), ('imaginable', 'JJ'), ('really', 'RB'), ('...', ':')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Muggles', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Muggles', 'NNP')])]","[Albus, all day]","(S
  (PERSON Albus/NNP)
  really/RB
  think/VBP
  's/POS
  safe/JJ
  leaving/VBG
  people/NNS
  've/VBP
  watched/VBN
  day/NN
  're/VBP
  worst/JJS
  sort/NN
  (PERSON Muggles/NNP)
  imaginable/JJ
  really/RB
  .../:)"
11,1,8,4,The only family he has.,['family'],Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('family', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S family/NN)
12,1,8,7,This boy will be famous. There won't be a child in our world who doesn't know his name.,"['boy', 'famous', 'wo', ""n't"", 'child', 'world', ""n't"", 'know', 'name']",Minerva McGonagall,Female,Gryffindor,"[('boy', 'RB'), ('famous', 'JJ'), ('wo', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('child', 'VB'), ('world', 'NN'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('know', 'VB'), ('name', 'NN')]",[],[],[],"(S
  boy/RB
  famous/JJ
  wo/MD
  n't/RB
  child/VB
  world/NN
  n't/RB
  know/VB
  name/NN)"
13,1,8,4,Exactly. He's better off growing up away from all that. Until he is ready.,"['Exactly', ""'s"", 'better', 'growing', 'away', 'ready']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Exactly', 'RB'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('better', 'RBR'), ('growing', 'VBG'), ('away', 'RB'), ('ready', 'JJ')]",[],[],[],(S Exactly/RB 's/POS better/RBR growing/VBG away/RB ready/JJ)
14,1,8,4,"There, there, Hagrid. It's not really goodbye, after all.","['Hagrid', ""'s"", 'really', 'goodbye']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Hagrid', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('really', 'RB'), ('goodbye', 'JJ')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],(S (GPE Hagrid/NNP) 's/POS really/RB goodbye/JJ)
15,1,8,4,Good luck...Harry Potter.,"['Good', 'luck', '...', 'Harry', 'Potter']",Albus Dumbledore,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Good', 'JJ'), ('luck', 'NN'), ('...', ':'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Good', 'JJ')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]",[Harry Potter],(S (GPE Good/JJ) luck/NN .../: (PERSON Harry/NNP Potter/NNP))
16,2,8,32,Up. Get up.  Now!,['Get'],Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('Get', 'VB')]",[],[],[],(S Get/VB)
17,2,8,31,"Wake up, cousin! We're going to the zoo!","['Wake', 'cousin', ""'re"", 'going', 'zoo']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Wake', 'NNP'), ('cousin', 'NN'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('zoo', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Wake', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (GPE Wake/NNP) cousin/NN 're/VBP going/VBG zoo/NN)
18,2,8,32,"Oh, here he comes, the birthday boy!","['Oh', 'comes', 'birthday', 'boy']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('comes', 'VBZ'), ('birthday', 'JJ'), ('boy', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S Oh/UH comes/VBZ birthday/JJ boy/NN)
19,2,8,21,"Happy birthday, son.","['Happy', 'birthday', 'son']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Happy', 'JJ'), ('birthday', 'NN'), ('son', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Happy', 'JJ')])]",[],(S (GPE Happy/JJ) birthday/NN son/NN)
20,2,8,32,"Why don't you just cook the breakfast, and try not to burn anything.","[""n't"", 'cook', 'breakfast', 'try', 'burn', 'anything']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[(""n't"", 'RB'), ('cook', 'VB'), ('breakfast', 'NN'), ('try', 'NN'), ('burn', 'NN'), ('anything', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S n't/RB cook/VB breakfast/NN try/NN burn/NN anything/NN)
21,2,8,1,"Yes, Aunt Petunia.","['Yes', 'Aunt', 'Petunia']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Yes', 'UH'), ('Aunt', 'NNP'), ('Petunia', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Aunt', 'NNP'), ('Petunia', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Aunt', 'NNP'), ('Petunia', 'NNP')])]",[Aunt Petunia],(S Yes/UH (PERSON Aunt/NNP Petunia/NNP))
22,2,8,32,I want everything to be perfect for my Dudley's special day.,"['want', 'everything', 'perfect', 'Dudley', ""'s"", 'special', 'day']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('want', 'NN'), ('everything', 'NN'), ('perfect', 'VBP'), ('Dudley', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('special', 'JJ'), ('day', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dudley', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dudley', 'NNP')])]","[Dudley, special day]","(S
  want/NN
  everything/NN
  perfect/VBP
  (PERSON Dudley/NNP)
  's/POS
  special/JJ
  day/NN)"
23,2,8,21,"Hurry up! Bring my coffee, boy!","['Hurry', 'Bring', 'coffee', 'boy']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Hurry', 'NNP'), ('Bring', 'NNP'), ('coffee', 'NN'), ('boy', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hurry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hurry', 'NNP')])]",[Hurry],(S (PERSON Hurry/NNP) Bring/NNP coffee/NN boy/NN)
24,2,8,1,"Yes, Uncle Vernon.","['Yes', 'Uncle', 'Vernon']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Yes', 'UH'), ('Uncle', 'NNP'), ('Vernon', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Uncle', 'NNP'), ('Vernon', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Uncle', 'NNP'), ('Vernon', 'NNP')])]",[Uncle Vernon],(S Yes/UH (PERSON Uncle/NNP Vernon/NNP))
25,2,8,32,"Aren't they wonderful, darling?","[""n't"", 'wonderful', 'darling']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[(""n't"", 'RB'), ('wonderful', 'JJ'), ('darling', 'VBG')]",[],[],[],(S n't/RB wonderful/JJ darling/VBG)
26,2,8,31,How many are there?,['many'],Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('many', 'JJ')]",[],[],[],(S many/JJ)
27,2,8,21,Thirty-six. Counted 'em myself.,"['Thirty-six', 'Counted', ""'em""]",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Thirty-six', 'NNP'), ('Counted', 'NNP'), (""'em"", 'POS')]",[],[],[Thirty-six],(S Thirty-six/NNP Counted/NNP 'em/POS)
28,2,8,31,Thirty-six?! But last year last year I had thirty-seven!!,"['Thirty-six', 'last', 'year', 'last', 'year', 'thirty-seven']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Thirty-six', 'CD'), ('last', 'JJ'), ('year', 'NN'), ('last', 'JJ'), ('year', 'NN'), ('thirty-seven', 'RB')]",[],[],"[Thirty-six, last year last year, thirty-seven]",(S Thirty-six/CD last/JJ year/NN last/JJ year/NN thirty-seven/RB)
29,2,8,21,"Err yes, well, some of them are quite a bit bigger than last year.","['Err', 'yes', 'well', 'quite', 'bit', 'bigger', 'last', 'year']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Err', 'NNP'), ('yes', 'RB'), ('well', 'RB'), ('quite', 'RB'), ('bit', 'NN'), ('bigger', 'JJR'), ('last', 'JJ'), ('year', 'NN')]",[],[],"[Err, last year]",(S Err/NNP yes/RB well/RB quite/RB bit/NN bigger/JJR last/JJ year/NN)
30,2,8,31,I don't care how big they are!,"[""n't"", 'care', 'big']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[(""n't"", 'RB'), ('care', 'VB'), ('big', 'JJ')]",[],[],[],(S n't/RB care/VB big/JJ)
31,2,8,32,"Oh, now, now, now. This is what we're going to do, is that when we go out, we're going to buy you two new presents! How's that, pumpkin?","['Oh', ""'re"", 'going', 'go', ""'re"", 'going', 'buy', 'two', 'new', 'presents', ""'s"", 'pumpkin']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('Oh', 'UH'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('go', 'VB'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('buy', 'VB'), ('two', 'CD'), ('new', 'JJ'), ('presents', 'NNS'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('pumpkin', 'NN')]",[],[],[two],"(S
  Oh/UH
  're/VBP
  going/VBG
  go/VB
  're/VBP
  going/VBG
  buy/VB
  two/CD
  new/JJ
  presents/NNS
  's/POS
  pumpkin/NN)"
32,2,8,32,This will be a lovely day at the zoo. I'm really looking forward to it.,"['lovely', 'day', 'zoo', ""'m"", 'really', 'looking', 'forward']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('lovely', 'RB'), ('day', 'NN'), ('zoo', 'NNP'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('really', 'RB'), ('looking', 'VBG'), ('forward', 'NN')]",[],[],[a lovely day],(S lovely/RB day/NN zoo/NNP 'm/VBP really/RB looking/VBG forward/NN)
33,2,8,21,"I'm warning you now, boy. Any funny business, any at all, and you won't have any meals for a week. Get in.","[""'m"", 'warning', 'boy', 'funny', 'business', 'wo', ""n't"", 'meals', 'week', 'Get']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[(""'m"", 'VBP'), ('warning', 'VBG'), ('boy', 'NN'), ('funny', 'JJ'), ('business', 'NN'), ('wo', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('meals', 'VB'), ('week', 'NN'), ('Get', 'NNP')]",[],[],[a week],"(S
  'm/VBP
  warning/VBG
  boy/NN
  funny/JJ
  business/NN
  wo/MD
  n't/RB
  meals/VB
  week/NN
  Get/NNP)"
34,2,8,31,Make it move.,"['Make', 'move']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Make', 'NNP'), ('move', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Make', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (GPE Make/NNP) move/NN)
35,2,8,21,Move!,['Move'],Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Move', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Move', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Move/NN))
36,2,8,31,MOVE!,['MOVE'],Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('MOVE', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('MOVE', 'NN')])]",[],(S (ORGANIZATION MOVE/NN))
37,2,8,1,He's asleep!,"[""'s"", 'asleep']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('asleep', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S 's/POS asleep/NN)
38,2,8,31,He's boring.,"[""'s"", 'boring']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('boring', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S 's/POS boring/NN)
39,2,8,1,"Sorry about him. He doesn't understand what it's like, lying there day after day, having people press their ugly faces in on you.  Can you...hear me?  It's just...I've never talked to a snake before. Do you...I mean...do you talk to people often?  You're from Burma, aren't you? Was it nice there, do you miss your family?  I see. That's me as well. I never knew my parents, either.","['Sorry', ""n't"", 'understand', ""'s"", 'like', 'lying', 'day', 'day', 'people', 'press', 'ugly', 'faces', '...', 'hear', ""'s"", '...', ""'ve"", 'never', 'talked', 'snake', '...', 'mean', '...', 'talk', 'people', 'often', ""'re"", 'Burma', ""n't"", 'nice', 'miss', 'family', 'see', ""'s"", 'well', 'never', 'knew', 'parents', 'either']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Sorry', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('understand', 'VB'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('like', 'IN'), ('lying', 'VBG'), ('day', 'NN'), ('day', 'NN'), ('people', 'NNS'), ('press', 'VBP'), ('ugly', 'RB'), ('faces', 'VBZ'), ('...', ':'), ('hear', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('...', ':'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('never', 'RB'), ('talked', 'VBN'), ('snake', 'NN'), ('...', ':'), ('mean', 'NN'), ('...', ':'), ('talk', 'NN'), ('people', 'NNS'), ('often', 'RB'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('Burma', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('nice', 'JJ'), ('miss', 'JJ'), ('family', 'NN'), ('see', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('well', 'RB'), ('never', 'RB'), ('knew', 'VBD'), ('parents', 'NNS'), ('either', 'CC')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Burma', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Burma', 'NNP')])]",[Burma],"(S
  (PERSON Sorry/NNP)
  n't/RB
  understand/VB
  's/POS
  like/IN
  lying/VBG
  day/NN
  day/NN
  people/NNS
  press/VBP
  ugly/RB
  faces/VBZ
  .../:
  hear/NN
  's/POS
  .../:
  've/VBP
  never/RB
  talked/VBN
  snake/NN
  .../:
  mean/NN
  .../:
  talk/NN
  people/NNS
  often/RB
  're/VBP
  (PERSON Burma/NNP)
  n't/RB
  nice/JJ
  miss/JJ
  family/NN
  see/NN
  's/POS
  well/RB
  never/RB
  knew/VBD
  parents/NNS
  either/CC)"
40,2,8,31,"Mummy, dad, come here! You won't believe what this snake is doing!","['Mummy', 'dad', 'come', 'wo', ""n't"", 'believe', 'snake']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Mummy', 'NNP'), ('dad', 'VBZ'), ('come', 'VB'), ('wo', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('believe', 'VB'), ('snake', 'VB')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Mummy', 'NNP')])]",[Mummy],(S (GPE Mummy/NNP) dad/VBZ come/VB wo/MD n't/RB believe/VB snake/VB)
41,2,8,31,Whoa! Ahh! Ahh!!,"['Whoa', 'Ahh', 'Ahh']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Whoa', 'NNP'), ('Ahh', 'NNP'), ('Ahh', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Whoa', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Whoa', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Ahh', 'NNP'), ('Ahh', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Whoa/NNP) (ORGANIZATION Ahh/NNP Ahh/NNP))
42,2,8,161,Thanks.,['Thanks'],Student,,,"[('Thanks', 'NNS')]",[],[],[],(S Thanks/NNS)
43,2,8,1,Anytime.,['Anytime'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Anytime', 'RB')]",[],[],[],(S Anytime/RB)
44,2,8,139,SNAKE!,['SNAKE'],Man,,,"[('SNAKE', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('SNAKE', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE SNAKE/NN))
45,2,8,31,"Mum, mummy!","['Mum', 'mummy']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Mum', 'NNP'), ('mummy', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Mum', 'NNP')])]",[mummy],(S (GPE Mum/NNP) mummy/NN)
46,2,8,32,AHH!,['AHH'],Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('AHH', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('AHH', 'NN')])]",[],(S (ORGANIZATION AHH/NN))
47,2,8,31,"Mum, help! Help me!","['Mum', 'help', 'Help']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Mum', 'NNP'), ('help', 'NN'), ('Help', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Help', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Mum', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Help', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (GPE Mum/NNP) help/NN (PERSON Help/NNP))
48,2,8,32,"My darling boy! How did you get in there?! How did you get in there? Dursley, oh, Dursley!","['darling', 'boy', 'get', 'get', 'Dursley', 'oh', 'Dursley']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('darling', 'VBG'), ('boy', 'NN'), ('get', 'VB'), ('get', 'VB'), ('Dursley', 'NNP'), ('oh', 'UH'), ('Dursley', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dursley', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Dursley', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dursley', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Dursley', 'NNP')])]","[Dursley, Dursley]","(S
  darling/VBG
  boy/NN
  get/VB
  get/VB
  (PERSON Dursley/NNP)
  oh/UH
  (PERSON Dursley/NNP))"
49,3,8,32,It's all right. It's all right.,"[""'s"", 'right', ""'s"", 'right']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('right', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('right', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S 's/POS right/NN 's/POS right/NN)
50,3,8,1,Ow!,['Ow'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Ow', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Ow', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Ow/NN))
51,3,8,21,What happened?!,['happened'],Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('happened', 'VBD')]",[],[],[],(S happened/VBD)
52,3,8,1,"I swear I don't know!  One minute, the glass was there and then it was gone! It was like magic!","['swear', ""n't"", 'know', 'One', 'minute', 'glass', 'gone', 'like', 'magic']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('swear', 'VBP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('know', 'VB'), ('One', 'CD'), ('minute', 'NN'), ('glass', 'NN'), ('gone', 'VBN'), ('like', 'IN'), ('magic', 'NN')]",[],[],[One minute],"(S
  swear/VBP
  n't/RB
  know/VB
  One/CD
  minute/NN
  glass/NN
  gone/VBN
  like/IN
  magic/NN)"
53,3,8,21,There's no such thing as magic!,"[""'s"", 'thing', 'magic']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('thing', 'NN'), ('magic', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S 's/POS thing/NN magic/NN)
54,3,8,32,"Awww, smile.  Vernon, just look at him. I can't believe it. In just a week you'll be off to Smeltings.","['Awww', 'smile', 'Vernon', 'look', 'ca', ""n't"", 'believe', 'week', ""'ll"", 'Smeltings']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('Awww', 'NNP'), ('smile', 'NN'), ('Vernon', 'NNP'), ('look', 'NN'), ('ca', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('believe', 'VB'), ('week', 'NN'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('Smeltings', 'VB')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Vernon', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Awww', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Vernon', 'NNP')])]","[Awww, Vernon, just a week, Smeltings]","(S
  (GPE Awww/NNP)
  smile/NN
  (PERSON Vernon/NNP)
  look/NN
  ca/MD
  n't/RB
  believe/VB
  week/NN
  'll/MD
  Smeltings/VB)"
55,3,8,21,Caveat Smeltona. Proudest moment of my life.,"['Caveat', 'Smeltona', 'Proudest', 'moment', 'life']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Caveat', 'NNP'), ('Smeltona', 'NNP'), ('Proudest', 'NNP'), ('moment', 'NN'), ('life', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Caveat', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Smeltona', 'NNP'), ('Proudest', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Caveat', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Smeltona', 'NNP'), ('Proudest', 'NNP')])]",[Caveat Smeltona],"(S
  (PERSON Caveat/NNP)
  (PERSON Smeltona/NNP Proudest/NNP)
  moment/NN
  life/NN)"
56,3,8,1,"Will I have to wear that, too?",['wear'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('wear', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S wear/NN)
57,3,8,32,"What, you? Go to Smeltings?","['Go', 'Smeltings']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('Go', 'NNP'), ('Smeltings', 'NNP')]",[],[],[Smeltings],(S Go/NNP Smeltings/NNP)
58,3,8,21,Ha!,['Ha'],Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Ha', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Ha', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Ha/NN))
59,3,8,32,"Oh, don't be so stupid, you're going to the state school where you belong.  And this is what you're gonna be wearing when I've finished dyeing it.","['Oh', ""n't"", 'stupid', ""'re"", 'going', 'state', 'school', 'belong', ""'re"", 'gon', 'na', 'wearing', ""'ve"", 'finished', 'dyeing']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('Oh', 'UH'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('stupid', 'JJ'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('state', 'NN'), ('school', 'NN'), ('belong', 'NN'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('gon', 'NN'), ('na', 'TO'), ('wearing', 'VBG'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('finished', 'VBN'), ('dyeing', 'NN')]",[],[],[],"(S
  Oh/UH
  n't/RB
  stupid/JJ
  're/VBP
  going/VBG
  state/NN
  school/NN
  belong/NN
  're/VBP
  gon/NN
  na/TO
  wearing/VBG
  've/VBP
  finished/VBN
  dyeing/NN)"
60,3,8,1,But that's Dudley's old uniform. It'll fit me like bits of old Elephant skin.,"[""'s"", 'Dudley', ""'s"", 'old', 'uniform', ""'ll"", 'fit', 'like', 'bits', 'old', 'Elephant', 'skin']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('Dudley', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('old', 'JJ'), ('uniform', 'JJ'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('fit', 'VB'), ('like', 'IN'), ('bits', 'NNS'), ('old', 'JJ'), ('Elephant', 'NNP'), ('skin', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dudley', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dudley', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Elephant', 'NNP')])]",[Dudley],"(S
  's/POS
  (PERSON Dudley/NNP)
  's/POS
  old/JJ
  uniform/JJ
  'll/MD
  fit/VB
  like/IN
  bits/NNS
  old/JJ
  (ORGANIZATION Elephant/NNP)
  skin/NN)"
61,3,8,32,It'll fit you well enough. Go get the post.  Go!,"[""'ll"", 'fit', 'well', 'enough', 'Go', 'get', 'post', 'Go']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[(""'ll"", 'MD'), ('fit', 'VB'), ('well', 'RB'), ('enough', 'RB'), ('Go', 'NNP'), ('get', 'VB'), ('post', 'RB'), ('Go', 'NNP')]",[],[],[],(S 'll/MD fit/VB well/RB enough/RB Go/NNP get/VB post/RB Go/NNP)
62,3,8,21,"Oh, Marge is ill! Ate a funny whelk.","['Oh', 'Marge', 'ill', 'Ate', 'funny', 'whelk']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('Marge', 'NNP'), ('ill', 'JJ'), ('Ate', 'NNP'), ('funny', 'NN'), ('whelk', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Marge', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Marge', 'NNP')])]",[Marge],(S Oh/UH (PERSON Marge/NNP) ill/JJ Ate/NNP funny/NN whelk/NN)
63,3,8,31,Dad! Look! Harry's got a letter!,"['Dad', 'Look', 'Harry', ""'s"", 'got', 'letter']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Dad', 'NNP'), ('Look', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('letter', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Dad', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Look', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],"(S
  (GPE Dad/NNP)
  (ORGANIZATION Look/NNP Harry/NNP)
  's/POS
  got/VBD
  letter/NN)"
64,3,8,1,"Hey, give it back! It's mine!","['Hey', 'give', 'back', ""'s"", 'mine']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Hey', 'NNP'), ('give', 'VBP'), ('back', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('mine', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S Hey/NNP give/VBP back/NN 's/POS mine/NN)
65,3,8,21,Yours? Who'd be writing to you?,"[""'d"", 'writing']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[(""'d"", 'MD'), ('writing', 'VBG')]",[],[],[],(S 'd/MD writing/VBG)
66,3,8,21,No more mail through this letterbox.,"['mail', 'letterbox']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('mail', 'NN'), ('letterbox', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S mail/NN letterbox/NN)
67,3,8,32,"Have a lovely day at the office, dear.","['lovely', 'day', 'office', 'dear']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('lovely', 'RB'), ('day', 'NN'), ('office', 'NN'), ('dear', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S lovely/RB day/NN office/NN dear/NN)
68,3,8,21,Shoo! Go on!,"['Shoo', 'Go']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Shoo', 'NNP'), ('Go', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Shoo', 'NNP'), ('Go', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Shoo', 'NNP'), ('Go', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Shoo/NNP Go/NNP))
69,3,8,21,"Fine day Sunday. In my opinion, best day of the week. Why is that, Dudley?","['Fine', 'day', 'Sunday', 'opinion', 'best', 'day', 'week', 'Dudley']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Fine', 'NNP'), ('day', 'NN'), ('Sunday', 'NNP'), ('opinion', 'NN'), ('best', 'RB'), ('day', 'NN'), ('week', 'NN'), ('Dudley', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dudley', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Fine', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Dudley', 'NNP')])]","[Sunday, best day of the week, Dudley]","(S
  (GPE Fine/NNP)
  day/NN
  Sunday/NNP
  opinion/NN
  best/RB
  day/NN
  week/NN
  (PERSON Dudley/NNP))"
70,3,8,1,Because there's no post on Sunday?,"[""'s"", 'post', 'Sunday']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('post', 'NN'), ('Sunday', 'NNP')]",[],[],[Sunday],(S 's/POS post/NN Sunday/NNP)
71,3,8,21,"Ah, right you are, Harry. No post on Sunday. Ha! No blasted letters today. No, sir. Not one single bloody letter, not one.  No, sir, not one blasted, miserable-","['Ah', 'right', 'Harry', 'post', 'Sunday', 'Ha', 'blasted', 'letters', 'today', 'sir', 'one', 'single', 'bloody', 'letter', 'one', 'sir', 'one', 'blasted', 'miserable-']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Ah', 'NNP'), ('right', 'NN'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('post', 'NN'), ('Sunday', 'NNP'), ('Ha', 'NNP'), ('blasted', 'VBD'), ('letters', 'NNS'), ('today', 'NN'), ('sir', 'VBP'), ('one', 'CD'), ('single', 'JJ'), ('bloody', 'NN'), ('letter', 'NN'), ('one', 'CD'), ('sir', 'NN'), ('one', 'CD'), ('blasted', 'VBD'), ('miserable-', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Ah', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Sunday, today, one]","(S
  (GPE Ah/NNP)
  right/NN
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  post/NN
  Sunday/NNP
  Ha/NNP
  blasted/VBD
  letters/NNS
  today/NN
  sir/VBP
  one/CD
  single/JJ
  bloody/NN
  letter/NN
  one/CD
  sir/NN
  one/CD
  blasted/VBD
  miserable-/NN)"
72,3,8,31,AHH! Make it stop! Please make it stop!,"['AHH', 'Make', 'stop', 'Please', 'make', 'stop']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('AHH', 'NNP'), ('Make', 'NNP'), ('stop', 'JJ'), ('Please', 'NNP'), ('make', 'VB'), ('stop', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('AHH', 'NNP')]), Tree('GPE', [('Make', 'NNP')])]",[],"(S
  (ORGANIZATION AHH/NNP)
  (GPE Make/NNP)
  stop/JJ
  Please/NNP
  make/VB
  stop/NN)"
73,3,8,21,"Go away, ahh!","['Go', 'away', 'ahh']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Go', 'VB'), ('away', 'RP'), ('ahh', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S Go/VB away/RP ahh/NN)
74,3,8,31,What is it? Please tell me what's happening!,"['Please', 'tell', ""'s"", 'happening']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Please', 'NNP'), ('tell', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('happening', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Please', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (GPE Please/NNP) tell/NN 's/POS happening/NN)
75,3,8,21,Give me that! Give me that letter!,"['Give', 'Give', 'letter']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Give', 'VB'), ('Give', 'NNP'), ('letter', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Give', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Give', 'NNP')])]",[],(S Give/VB (PERSON Give/NNP) letter/NN)
76,3,8,1,Get off! Ahh!,"['Get', 'Ahh']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Get', 'NNP'), ('Ahh', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Get', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Get', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Ahh', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Get/NNP) (ORGANIZATION Ahh/NNP))
77,3,8,21,Ahh!,['Ahh'],Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('Ahh', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Ahh', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Ahh/NN))
78,3,8,1,They're my letters! Let go of me!,"[""'re"", 'letters', 'Let', 'go']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'re"", 'VBP'), ('letters', 'NNS'), ('Let', 'NNP'), ('go', 'VB')]",[],[],[],(S 're/VBP letters/NNS Let/NNP go/VB)
79,3,8,21,That's it! We're going away! Far away! Where they can't find us!,"[""'s"", ""'re"", 'going', 'away', 'Far', 'away', 'ca', ""n't"", 'find', 'us']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('away', 'RB'), ('Far', 'NNP'), ('away', 'RB'), ('ca', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('find', 'VB'), ('us', 'PRP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Far', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Far', 'NNP')])]",[],"(S
  's/POS
  're/VBP
  going/VBG
  away/RB
  (PERSON Far/NNP)
  away/RB
  ca/MD
  n't/RB
  find/VB
  us/PRP)"
80,3,8,31,"Daddy's gone mad, hasn't he?!","['Daddy', ""'s"", 'gone', 'mad', ""n't""]",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Daddy', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('gone', 'VBN'), ('mad', 'JJ'), (""n't"", 'RB')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Daddy', 'NNP')])]",[Daddy],(S (GPE Daddy/NNP) 's/POS gone/VBN mad/JJ n't/RB)
81,4,10,1,"Make a wish, Harry.","['Make', 'wish', 'Harry']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Make', 'NNP'), ('wish', 'JJ'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Make', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S (GPE Make/NNP) wish/JJ (PERSON Harry/NNP))
82,4,10,21,Who's there? Ahh!,"[""'s"", 'Ahh']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('Ahh', 'NNP')]",[],[],[],(S 's/POS Ahh/NNP)
83,4,10,5,Sorry 'bout that.,"['Sorry', ""'bout""]",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Sorry', 'NNP'), (""'bout"", 'POS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Sorry/NNP) 'bout/POS)
84,4,10,21,"I demand that you leave at once, sir! You are breaking and entering!","['demand', 'leave', 'sir', 'breaking', 'entering']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('demand', 'NN'), ('leave', 'VBP'), ('sir', 'VBN'), ('breaking', 'VBG'), ('entering', 'VBG')]",[],[],[],(S demand/NN leave/VBP sir/VBN breaking/VBG entering/VBG)
85,4,10,5,"Dry up, Dursley, you great prune.  Boy, I haven't seen you since you was a baby, Harry, but you're a bit more along than I would have expected. Particularly 'round the middle!","['Dry', 'Dursley', 'great', 'prune', 'Boy', ""n't"", 'seen', 'since', 'baby', 'Harry', ""'re"", 'bit', 'along', 'would', 'expected', 'Particularly', ""'round"", 'middle']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Dry', 'NNP'), ('Dursley', 'NNP'), ('great', 'JJ'), ('prune', 'NN'), ('Boy', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('seen', 'VBN'), ('since', 'IN'), ('baby', 'NN'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('bit', 'NN'), ('along', 'RB'), ('would', 'MD'), ('expected', 'VBN'), ('Particularly', 'RB'), (""'round"", 'CD'), ('middle', 'NNS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Dursley', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Dry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Dursley', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Dursley, Harry]","(S
  (PERSON Dry/NNP)
  (PERSON Dursley/NNP)
  great/JJ
  prune/NN
  Boy/NNP
  n't/RB
  seen/VBN
  since/IN
  baby/NN
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  're/VBP
  bit/NN
  along/RB
  would/MD
  expected/VBN
  Particularly/RB
  'round/CD
  middle/NNS)"
86,4,10,31,I-I-I'm not Harry.,"['I-I-I', ""'m"", 'Harry']",Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('I-I-I', 'NNP'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S I-I-I/NNP 'm/VBP (PERSON Harry/NNP))
87,4,10,1,I-I am.,['I-I'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('I-I', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S I-I/NN)
88,4,10,5,"Oh, well, of course you are! Got something for ya. 'Fraid I might have sat on it at some point! I imagine that it'll taste fine just the same. Ahh. Baked it myself.  Words and all. Heh.","['Oh', 'well', 'course', 'Got', 'something', 'ya', ""'Fraid"", 'might', 'sat', 'point', 'imagine', ""'ll"", 'taste', 'fine', 'Ahh', 'Baked', 'Words', 'Heh']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('well', 'RB'), ('course', 'NN'), ('Got', 'NNP'), ('something', 'NN'), ('ya', 'NNS'), (""'Fraid"", 'POS'), ('might', 'MD'), ('sat', 'VB'), ('point', 'NN'), ('imagine', 'NN'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('taste', 'VB'), ('fine', 'JJ'), ('Ahh', 'NNP'), ('Baked', 'NNP'), ('Words', 'NNP'), ('Heh', 'NNP')]",[],[],[],"(S
  Oh/UH
  well/RB
  course/NN
  Got/NNP
  something/NN
  ya/NNS
  'Fraid/POS
  might/MD
  sat/VB
  point/NN
  imagine/NN
  'll/MD
  taste/VB
  fine/JJ
  Ahh/NNP
  Baked/NNP
  Words/NNP
  Heh/NNP)"
89,4,10,1,Thank you!,['Thank'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Thank', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Thank', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Thank/NN))
90,4,10,5,"It's not every day that your young man turns eleven, now is it?","[""'s"", 'every', 'day', 'young', 'man', 'turns', 'eleven']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('every', 'DT'), ('day', 'NN'), ('young', 'JJ'), ('man', 'NN'), ('turns', 'VBZ'), ('eleven', 'RB')]",[],[],[eleven],(S 's/POS every/DT day/NN young/JJ man/NN turns/VBZ eleven/RB)
91,4,10,1,"Excuse me, who are you?",['Excuse'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Excuse', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Excuse', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Excuse/NN))
92,4,10,5,"Rubeus Hagrid. Keeper of keys and grounds at Hogwarts. Course, you'll know all about Hogwarts.","['Rubeus', 'Hagrid', 'Keeper', 'keys', 'grounds', 'Hogwarts', 'Course', ""'ll"", 'know', 'Hogwarts']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Rubeus', 'NNP'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('Keeper', 'NNP'), ('keys', 'NNP'), ('grounds', 'VBZ'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('Course', 'NNP'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('know', 'VB'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Rubeus', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('Keeper', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('Course', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Rubeus', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('Keeper', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('Course', 'NNP')])]",[Rubeus Hagrid],"(S
  (PERSON Rubeus/NNP)
  (PERSON Hagrid/NNP Keeper/NNP)
  keys/NNP
  grounds/VBZ
  (PERSON Hogwarts/NNP Course/NNP)
  'll/MD
  know/VB
  Hogwarts/NNS)"
93,4,10,1,"Sorry, no.",['Sorry'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Sorry', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NN')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NN')])]",[],(S (PERSON Sorry/NN))
94,4,10,5,"No? Blimey, Harry, didn't you ever wonder where your mum and dad learned it all?","['Blimey', 'Harry', ""n't"", 'ever', 'wonder', 'mum', 'dad', 'learned']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Blimey', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('ever', 'RB'), ('wonder', 'VB'), ('mum', 'JJ'), ('dad', 'NN'), ('learned', 'VBD')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Blimey', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Blimey', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],"(S
  (PERSON Blimey/NNP)
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  n't/RB
  ever/RB
  wonder/VB
  mum/JJ
  dad/NN
  learned/VBD)"
95,4,10,1,Learned what?,['Learned'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Learned', 'VBN')]",[],[],[],(S Learned/VBN)
96,4,10,5,"You're a wizard, Harry.","[""'re"", 'wizard', 'Harry']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'re"", 'VBP'), ('wizard', 'NN'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S 're/VBP wizard/NN (PERSON Harry/NNP))
97,4,10,1,I-I'm a what?,"['I-I', ""'m""]",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('I-I', 'JJ'), (""'m"", 'VBP')]",[],[],[],(S I-I/JJ 'm/VBP)
98,4,10,5,"A wizard. And a thumping good one at that, I'd wager. Once you train up a little.","['wizard', 'thumping', 'good', 'one', ""'d"", 'wager', 'train', 'little']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('wizard', 'RB'), ('thumping', 'VBG'), ('good', 'JJ'), ('one', 'CD'), (""'d"", 'MD'), ('wager', 'VB'), ('train', 'VB'), ('little', 'JJ')]",[],[],[],"(S
  wizard/RB
  thumping/VBG
  good/JJ
  one/CD
  'd/MD
  wager/VB
  train/VB
  little/JJ)"
99,4,10,1,"No, you've made a mistake. I can't be...a-a wizard. I mean, I'm just... Harry. Just Harry.","[""'ve"", 'made', 'mistake', 'ca', ""n't"", '...', 'a-a', 'wizard', 'mean', ""'m"", '...', 'Harry', 'Harry']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('made', 'VBN'), ('mistake', 'NN'), ('ca', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('...', ':'), ('a-a', 'JJ'), ('wizard', 'JJ'), ('mean', 'NN'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('...', ':'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Harry]","(S
  've/VBP
  made/VBN
  mistake/NN
  ca/MD
  n't/RB
  .../:
  a-a/JJ
  wizard/JJ
  mean/NN
  'm/VBP
  .../:
  (PERSON Harry/NNP Harry/NNP))"
100,4,10,5,"Well, just Harry. Did you ever make anything happen? Anything you couldn't explain when you were angry or scared?  Ah.","['Well', 'Harry', 'ever', 'make', 'anything', 'happen', 'Anything', 'could', ""n't"", 'explain', 'angry', 'scared', 'Ah']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Well', 'RB'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('ever', 'RB'), ('make', 'VBP'), ('anything', 'NN'), ('happen', 'JJ'), ('Anything', 'NNP'), ('could', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('explain', 'VB'), ('angry', 'JJ'), ('scared', 'VBN'), ('Ah', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],"(S
  Well/RB
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  ever/RB
  make/VBP
  anything/NN
  happen/JJ
  Anything/NNP
  could/MD
  n't/RB
  explain/VB
  angry/JJ
  scared/VBN
  Ah/NNP)"
101,4,10,1,"Dear, Mr. Potter. We are pleased to inform you that you have been accepted at Hogwarts' School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.","['Dear', 'Mr.', 'Potter', 'pleased', 'inform', 'accepted', 'Hogwarts', 'School', 'Witchcraft', 'Wizardry']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Dear', 'IN'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('pleased', 'VBD'), ('inform', 'NN'), ('accepted', 'VBN'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('School', 'NNP'), ('Witchcraft', 'NNP'), ('Wizardry', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('School', 'NNP'), ('Witchcraft', 'NNP'), ('Wizardry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('School', 'NNP'), ('Witchcraft', 'NNP'), ('Wizardry', 'NNP')])]","[Potter, Hogwarts' School of Witchcraft, Wizardry]","(S
  Dear/IN
  (PERSON Mr./NNP Potter/NNP)
  pleased/VBD
  inform/NN
  accepted/VBN
  (PERSON Hogwarts/NNP School/NNP Witchcraft/NNP Wizardry/NNP))"
102,4,10,21,"He'll not be going! We swore when we took him in, we'd put a stop to this rubbish!","[""'ll"", 'going', 'swore', 'took', ""'d"", 'put', 'stop', 'rubbish']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[(""'ll"", 'MD'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('swore', 'RB'), ('took', 'VBD'), (""'d"", 'MD'), ('put', 'VB'), ('stop', 'VB'), ('rubbish', 'NN')]",[],[],[],"(S
  'll/MD
  going/VBG
  swore/RB
  took/VBD
  'd/MD
  put/VB
  stop/VB
  rubbish/NN)"
103,4,10,1,You knew? You knew all along and you never told me?,"['knew', 'knew', 'along', 'never', 'told']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('knew', 'VB'), ('knew', 'NNS'), ('along', 'RB'), ('never', 'RB'), ('told', 'VBD')]",[],[],[],(S knew/VB knew/NNS along/RB never/RB told/VBD)
104,4,10,32,"Of course we knew. How could you not be? My perfect sister being who she was. Oh, my mother and father were so proud the day she got her letter. We have a witch in the family. Isn't it wonderful? I was the only one to see her for what she was. A freak! And then she met that Potter, and then she had you, and I knew you'd be just the same, just as strange, just as ... abnormal. And then, if you please, she went and got herself blown up. And we got landed with you.","['course', 'knew', 'could', 'perfect', 'sister', 'Oh', 'mother', 'father', 'proud', 'day', 'got', 'letter', 'witch', 'family', ""n't"", 'wonderful', 'one', 'see', 'freak', 'met', 'Potter', 'knew', ""'d"", 'strange', '...', 'abnormal', 'please', 'went', 'got', 'blown', 'got', 'landed']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('course', 'NN'), ('knew', 'NN'), ('could', 'MD'), ('perfect', 'VB'), ('sister', 'JJR'), ('Oh', 'NNP'), ('mother', 'NN'), ('father', 'NN'), ('proud', 'JJ'), ('day', 'NN'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('letter', 'NN'), ('witch', 'NN'), ('family', 'NN'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('wonderful', 'JJ'), ('one', 'CD'), ('see', 'NN'), ('freak', 'JJ'), ('met', 'VBD'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('knew', 'VBD'), (""'d"", 'MD'), ('strange', 'VB'), ('...', ':'), ('abnormal', 'JJ'), ('please', 'NN'), ('went', 'VBD'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('blown', 'JJ'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('landed', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[the day, Potter]","(S
  course/NN
  knew/NN
  could/MD
  perfect/VB
  sister/JJR
  Oh/NNP
  mother/NN
  father/NN
  proud/JJ
  day/NN
  got/VBD
  letter/NN
  witch/NN
  family/NN
  n't/RB
  wonderful/JJ
  one/CD
  see/NN
  freak/JJ
  met/VBD
  (PERSON Potter/NNP)
  knew/VBD
  'd/MD
  strange/VB
  .../:
  abnormal/JJ
  please/NN
  went/VBD
  got/VBD
  blown/JJ
  got/VBD
  landed/JJ)"
105,4,10,1,Blown up? You told me my parents died in a car crash!,"['Blown', 'told', 'parents', 'died', 'car', 'crash']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Blown', 'NNP'), ('told', 'VBD'), ('parents', 'NNS'), ('died', 'VBD'), ('car', 'NN'), ('crash', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Blown', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Blown', 'NNP')])]",[Blown],(S (PERSON Blown/NNP) told/VBD parents/NNS died/VBD car/NN crash/NN)
106,4,10,5,A car crash? A car crash kill James and Lily Potter?,"['car', 'crash', 'car', 'crash', 'kill', 'James', 'Lily', 'Potter']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('car', 'NN'), ('crash', 'NN'), ('car', 'NN'), ('crash', 'NN'), ('kill', 'NN'), ('James', 'NNP'), ('Lily', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('James', 'NNP'), ('Lily', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('James', 'NNP'), ('Lily', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[James, Lily Potter]","(S
  car/NN
  crash/NN
  car/NN
  crash/NN
  kill/NN
  (PERSON James/NNP Lily/NNP Potter/NNP))"
107,4,10,32,We had to tell him something.,"['tell', 'something']",Petunia Dursley,Female,,"[('tell', 'NN'), ('something', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S tell/NN something/NN)
108,4,10,5,It's an outrage! It's a scandal!,"[""'s"", 'outrage', ""'s"", 'scandal']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('outrage', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('scandal', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S 's/POS outrage/NN 's/POS scandal/NN)
109,4,10,21,He'll not be going!,"[""'ll"", 'going']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[(""'ll"", 'MD'), ('going', 'VBG')]",[],[],[],(S 'll/MD going/VBG)
110,4,10,5,"Oh, and I suppose a great Muggle like yourself's going to stop him, are you?","['Oh', 'suppose', 'great', 'Muggle', 'like', ""'s"", 'going', 'stop']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('suppose', 'JJ'), ('great', 'JJ'), ('Muggle', 'NNP'), ('like', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('stop', 'NN')]",[],[],[],"(S
  Oh/UH
  suppose/JJ
  great/JJ
  Muggle/NNP
  like/NN
  's/POS
  going/VBG
  stop/NN)"
111,4,10,1,Muggle?,['Muggle'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Muggle', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Muggle', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Muggle/NN))
112,4,10,5,"Non magic folk.  This boy's had his name down ever since he was born!  He's going to the finest school of witchcraft and wizardry in the world, and he'll be under the finest headmaster that Hogwarts has ever seen: Albus Dumbledore.","['Non', 'magic', 'folk', 'boy', ""'s"", 'name', 'ever', 'since', 'born', ""'s"", 'going', 'finest', 'school', 'witchcraft', 'wizardry', 'world', ""'ll"", 'finest', 'headmaster', 'Hogwarts', 'ever', 'seen', 'Albus', 'Dumbledore']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Non', 'NNP'), ('magic', 'JJ'), ('folk', 'NN'), ('boy', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('name', 'NN'), ('ever', 'RB'), ('since', 'IN'), ('born', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('finest', 'JJ'), ('school', 'NN'), ('witchcraft', 'NN'), ('wizardry', 'VBP'), ('world', 'NN'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('finest', 'VB'), ('headmaster', 'NN'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('ever', 'RB'), ('seen', 'VBN'), ('Albus', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Non', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP')])]","[Hogwarts, Albus Dumbledore]","(S
  (GPE Non/NNP)
  magic/JJ
  folk/NN
  boy/NN
  's/POS
  name/NN
  ever/RB
  since/IN
  born/NN
  's/POS
  going/VBG
  finest/JJ
  school/NN
  witchcraft/NN
  wizardry/VBP
  world/NN
  'll/MD
  finest/VB
  headmaster/NN
  (PERSON Hogwarts/NNP)
  ever/RB
  seen/VBN
  (PERSON Albus/NNP Dumbledore/NNP))"
113,4,10,21,I will not pay for some crackpot old fool to teach him magic tricks!,"['pay', 'crackpot', 'old', 'fool', 'teach', 'magic', 'tricks']",Vernon Dursley,Male,,"[('pay', 'NN'), ('crackpot', 'NN'), ('old', 'JJ'), ('fool', 'NN'), ('teach', 'NN'), ('magic', 'NN'), ('tricks', 'NNS')]",[],[],[],(S pay/NN crackpot/NN old/JJ fool/NN teach/NN magic/NN tricks/NNS)
114,4,10,5,"Never, insult Albus Dumbledore, in front of me.","['Never', 'insult', 'Albus', 'Dumbledore', 'front']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Never', 'RB'), ('insult', 'NN'), ('Albus', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP'), ('front', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Albus', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP')])]",[Albus Dumbledore],(S Never/RB insult/NN (PERSON Albus/NNP Dumbledore/NNP) front/NN)
115,4,10,31,Ahh!,['Ahh'],Dudley Dursley,Male,,"[('Ahh', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Ahh', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Ahh/NN))
116,4,10,5,"Oh, um, I'd appreciate if you didn't tell anyone at Hogwarts about that. Strictly speaking, I'm not allowed to do magic.","['Oh', 'um', ""'d"", 'appreciate', ""n't"", 'tell', 'anyone', 'Hogwarts', 'Strictly', 'speaking', ""'m"", 'allowed', 'magic']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('um', 'JJ'), (""'d"", 'MD'), ('appreciate', 'VB'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('tell', 'VB'), ('anyone', 'NN'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('Strictly', 'NNP'), ('speaking', 'VBG'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('allowed', 'VBN'), ('magic', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('Strictly', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('Strictly', 'NNP')])]",[],"(S
  Oh/UH
  um/JJ
  'd/MD
  appreciate/VB
  n't/RB
  tell/VB
  anyone/NN
  (PERSON Hogwarts/NNP Strictly/NNP)
  speaking/VBG
  'm/VBP
  allowed/VBN
  magic/NN)"
117,4,10,1,Okay.,['Okay'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Okay', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Okay', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Okay/NN))
118,4,10,5,"Ooh, we're a bit behind schedule. Best be off.  Unless you'd rather stay, of course. Hmm?","['Ooh', ""'re"", 'bit', 'behind', 'schedule', 'Best', 'Unless', ""'d"", 'rather', 'stay', 'course', 'Hmm']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Ooh', 'NNP'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('bit', 'NN'), ('behind', 'JJ'), ('schedule', 'NN'), ('Best', 'NNP'), ('Unless', 'NNP'), (""'d"", 'MD'), ('rather', 'RB'), ('stay', 'VB'), ('course', 'NN'), ('Hmm', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Best', 'NNP'), ('Unless', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Best', 'NNP'), ('Unless', 'NNP')])]",[],"(S
  Ooh/NNP
  're/VBP
  bit/NN
  behind/JJ
  schedule/NN
  (PERSON Best/NNP Unless/NNP)
  'd/MD
  rather/RB
  stay/VB
  course/NN
  Hmm/NNP)"
119,5,5,1,"First year students will require: three sets of work robes, one wand.","['First', 'year', 'students', 'require', 'three', 'sets', 'work', 'robes', 'one', 'wand']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('First', 'RB'), ('year', 'NN'), ('students', 'NNS'), ('require', 'VBP'), ('three', 'CD'), ('sets', 'NNS'), ('work', 'VBP'), ('robes', 'RB'), ('one', 'CD'), ('wand', 'NN')]",[],[],"[First year, three, one]","(S
  First/RB
  year/NN
  students/NNS
  require/VBP
  three/CD
  sets/NNS
  work/VBP
  robes/RB
  one/CD
  wand/NN)"
120,5,5,5,"Essential bit of equipment, Harry.","['Essential', 'bit', 'equipment', 'Harry']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Essential', 'JJ'), ('bit', 'NN'), ('equipment', 'NN'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Essential', 'JJ')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S (GPE Essential/JJ) bit/NN equipment/NN (PERSON Harry/NNP))
121,5,5,1,"One pair of dragon-hide gloves.  Hagrid, do they mean for a real dragon?","['One', 'pair', 'dragon-hide', 'gloves', 'Hagrid', 'mean', 'real', 'dragon']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('One', 'CD'), ('pair', 'NN'), ('dragon-hide', 'JJ'), ('gloves', 'NNS'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('mean', 'VBP'), ('real', 'JJ'), ('dragon', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[One, Hagrid]","(S
  One/CD
  pair/NN
  dragon-hide/JJ
  gloves/NNS
  (PERSON Hagrid/NNP)
  mean/VBP
  real/JJ
  dragon/NN)"
122,5,5,5,"Well, they don't mean for a penguin, do they? Heh. Crikey, but not a dragon.","['Well', ""n't"", 'mean', 'penguin', 'Heh', 'Crikey', 'dragon']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Well', 'RB'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('mean', 'VB'), ('penguin', 'JJ'), ('Heh', 'NNP'), ('Crikey', 'NNP'), ('dragon', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S Well/RB n't/RB mean/VB penguin/JJ Heh/NNP Crikey/NNP dragon/NN)
123,5,5,1,But you like a dragon?,"['like', 'dragon']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('like', 'IN'), ('dragon', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S like/IN dragon/NN)
124,5,5,5,"Fast and misunderstood beasts, Harry. Fast and misunderstood.","['Fast', 'misunderstood', 'beasts', 'Harry', 'Fast', 'misunderstood']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Fast', 'RB'), ('misunderstood', 'NN'), ('beasts', 'NNS'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Fast', 'NNP'), ('misunderstood', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Fast', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Fast', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],"(S
  Fast/RB
  misunderstood/NN
  beasts/NNS
  (PERSON Harry/NNP Fast/NNP)
  misunderstood/NN)"
125,5,5,1,"All students must be equipped with...one standard size two pewter cauldron and may bring if they desire either an owl, a cat or a toad. Could we find all this in London?","['students', 'must', 'equipped', '...', 'one', 'standard', 'size', 'two', 'pewter', 'cauldron', 'may', 'bring', 'desire', 'either', 'owl', 'cat', 'toad', 'Could', 'find', 'London']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('students', 'NNS'), ('must', 'MD'), ('equipped', 'VB'), ('...', ':'), ('one', 'CD'), ('standard', 'JJ'), ('size', 'NN'), ('two', 'CD'), ('pewter', 'NN'), ('cauldron', 'NN'), ('may', 'MD'), ('bring', 'VB'), ('desire', 'NN'), ('either', 'CC'), ('owl', 'JJ'), ('cat', 'NN'), ('toad', 'NN'), ('Could', 'NNP'), ('find', 'VBP'), ('London', 'NNP')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('London', 'NNP')])]","[one, two, London]","(S
  students/NNS
  must/MD
  equipped/VB
  .../:
  one/CD
  standard/JJ
  size/NN
  two/CD
  pewter/NN
  cauldron/NN
  may/MD
  bring/VB
  desire/NN
  either/CC
  owl/JJ
  cat/NN
  toad/NN
  Could/NNP
  find/VBP
  (GPE London/NNP))"
126,5,5,5,If you know where to go.,"['know', 'go']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('know', 'NNS'), ('go', 'VBP')]",[],[],[],(S know/NNS go/VBP)
127,5,5,92,"Ah, Hagrid! The usual, I presume?","['Ah', 'Hagrid', 'usual', 'presume']",Tom,Male,,"[('Ah', 'NNP'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('usual', 'JJ'), ('presume', 'NN')]",[],[],[Hagrid],(S Ah/NNP Hagrid/NNP usual/JJ presume/NN)
128,5,5,5,"No thanks, Tom. I'm on official Hogwarts business today. Just helping young Harry here buy his school supplies.","['thanks', 'Tom', ""'m"", 'official', 'Hogwarts', 'business', 'today', 'helping', 'young', 'Harry', 'buy', 'school', 'supplies']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('thanks', 'NNS'), ('Tom', 'NNP'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('official', 'JJ'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('business', 'NN'), ('today', 'NN'), ('helping', 'VBG'), ('young', 'JJ'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('buy', 'VB'), ('school', 'NN'), ('supplies', 'NNS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tom, Hogwarts, today, Harry]","(S
  thanks/NNS
  Tom/NNP
  'm/VBP
  official/JJ
  Hogwarts/NNP
  business/NN
  today/NN
  helping/VBG
  young/JJ
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  buy/VB
  school/NN
  supplies/NNS)"
129,5,5,92,Bless my soul. It's Harry Potter.,"['Bless', 'soul', ""'s"", 'Harry', 'Potter']",Tom,Male,,"[('Bless', 'NNP'), ('soul', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('Bless', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]",[Harry Potter],(S (GPE Bless/NNP) soul/NN 's/POS (PERSON Harry/NNP Potter/NNP))
130,5,5,139,"Welcome back, Mr. Potter, welcome back.","['Welcome', 'back', 'Mr.', 'Potter', 'welcome', 'back']",Man,,,"[('Welcome', 'NNP'), ('back', 'RB'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('welcome', 'VBD'), ('back', 'RP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]",[Potter],"(S
  Welcome/NNP
  back/RB
  (PERSON Mr./NNP Potter/NNP)
  welcome/VBD
  back/RP)"
131,5,5,132,"Doris Crockford, Mr. Potter. I can't believe I'm meeting you at last.","['Doris', 'Crockford', 'Mr.', 'Potter', 'ca', ""n't"", 'believe', ""'m"", 'meeting', 'last']",Goblin,,,"[('Doris', 'NNP'), ('Crockford', 'NNP'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('ca', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('believe', 'VB'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('meeting', 'NN'), ('last', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Doris', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Crockford', 'NNP'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Doris', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Crockford', 'NNP'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Doris Crockford, Potter]","(S
  (PERSON Doris/NNP)
  (PERSON Crockford/NNP Mr./NNP Potter/NNP)
  ca/MD
  n't/RB
  believe/VB
  'm/VBP
  meeting/NN
  last/JJ)"
132,5,5,41,Harry P-potter. C-can't tell you how pleased I am to meet you.,"['Harry', 'P-potter', 'C-ca', ""n't"", 'tell', 'pleased', 'meet']",Quirinus Quirrell,Male,Ravenclaw,"[('Harry', 'NNP'), ('P-potter', 'NNP'), ('C-ca', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('tell', 'VB'), ('pleased', 'JJ'), ('meet', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry P-potter],"(S
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  P-potter/NNP
  C-ca/NNP
  n't/RB
  tell/VB
  pleased/JJ
  meet/NN)"
133,5,5,5,"Hello, Professor. I didn't see you there. Harry, this is Professor Quirrell. He'll be your Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher at Hogwarts.","['Hello', 'Professor', ""n't"", 'see', 'Harry', 'Professor', 'Quirrell', ""'ll"", 'Defense', 'Dark', 'Arts', 'teacher', 'Hogwarts']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Hello', 'NNP'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('see', 'VB'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('Quirrell', 'NNP'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('Defense', 'NNP'), ('Dark', 'NNP'), ('Arts', 'NNP'), ('teacher', 'NN'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hello', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('Quirrell', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hello', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('Quirrell', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Defense', 'NNP'), ('Dark', 'NNP'), ('Arts', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Quirrell]","(S
  (PERSON Hello/NNP)
  Professor/NNP
  n't/RB
  see/VB
  (PERSON Harry/NNP Professor/NNP Quirrell/NNP)
  'll/MD
  (ORGANIZATION Defense/NNP Dark/NNP Arts/NNP)
  teacher/NN
  Hogwarts/NNS)"
134,5,5,1,"Oh, nice to meet you.","['Oh', 'nice', 'meet']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'NNP'), ('nice', 'JJ'), ('meet', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S Oh/NNP nice/JJ meet/NN)
135,5,5,41,"F-fearfully fascinating subject. N-not that you need it, e-eh, Potter? Heheh.","['F-fearfully', 'fascinating', 'subject', 'N-not', 'need', 'e-eh', 'Potter', 'Heheh']",Quirinus Quirrell,Male,Ravenclaw,"[('F-fearfully', 'RB'), ('fascinating', 'VBG'), ('subject', 'JJ'), ('N-not', 'NNP'), ('need', 'NN'), ('e-eh', 'JJ'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('Heheh', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Potter', 'NNP'), ('Heheh', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Potter', 'NNP'), ('Heheh', 'NNP')])]",[Potter],"(S
  F-fearfully/RB
  fascinating/VBG
  subject/JJ
  N-not/NNP
  need/NN
  e-eh/JJ
  (PERSON Potter/NNP Heheh/NNP))"
136,5,5,5,"Yes, well, must be going now. Lots to buy. Heh.","['Yes', 'well', 'must', 'going', 'Lots', 'buy', 'Heh']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Yes', 'UH'), ('well', 'RB'), ('must', 'MD'), ('going', 'VBG'), ('Lots', 'NNP'), ('buy', 'VB'), ('Heh', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Lots', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Lots', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Heh', 'NNP')])]",[],"(S
  Yes/UH
  well/RB
  must/MD
  going/VBG
  (PERSON Lots/NNP)
  buy/VB
  (ORGANIZATION Heh/NNP))"
137,5,5,1,Goodbye.,['Goodbye'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Goodbye', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Goodbye', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Goodbye/NN))
138,5,5,5,"See, Harry, you're famous!","['See', 'Harry', ""'re"", 'famous']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('See', 'VB'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('famous', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S See/VB (PERSON Harry/NNP) 're/VBP famous/JJ)
139,5,5,1,"But why am I famous, Hagrid? All those people back there, how is it they know who I am?","['famous', 'Hagrid', 'people', 'back', 'know']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('famous', 'JJ'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('people', 'NNS'), ('back', 'RB'), ('know', 'VBP')]",[],[],[Hagrid],(S famous/JJ Hagrid/NNP people/NNS back/RB know/VBP)
140,5,5,5,"I'm not exactly sure I'm the right person to tell you that, Harry.  Welcome, Harry, to Diagon Alley.  Here's where you'll get your quills and ink, and over there all your bits and bobs for doing your wizardry.","[""'m"", 'exactly', 'sure', ""'m"", 'right', 'person', 'tell', 'Harry', 'Welcome', 'Harry', 'Diagon', 'Alley', ""'s"", ""'ll"", 'get', 'quills', 'ink', 'bits', 'bobs', 'wizardry']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'m"", 'VBP'), ('exactly', 'RB'), ('sure', 'JJ'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('right', 'JJ'), ('person', 'NN'), ('tell', 'VB'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Welcome', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Diagon', 'NNP'), ('Alley', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('get', 'VB'), ('quills', 'NNS'), ('ink', 'VB'), ('bits', 'NNS'), ('bobs', 'VB'), ('wizardry', 'NNS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Welcome', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Diagon', 'NNP'), ('Alley', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Welcome', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Diagon', 'NNP'), ('Alley', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Harry, Diagon Alley]","(S
  'm/VBP
  exactly/RB
  sure/JJ
  'm/VBP
  right/JJ
  person/NN
  tell/VB
  (PERSON Harry/NNP Welcome/NNP Harry/NNP Diagon/NNP Alley/NNP)
  's/POS
  'll/MD
  get/VB
  quills/NNS
  ink/VB
  bits/NNS
  bobs/VB
  wizardry/NNS)"
141,5,5,138,"It's a world class racing broom. Look at it, it's the new Nimbus 2000! It's the fastest model yet.","[""'s"", 'world', 'class', 'racing', 'broom', 'Look', ""'s"", 'new', 'Nimbus', '2000', ""'s"", 'fastest', 'model', 'yet']",Boy,,,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('world', 'NN'), ('class', 'NN'), ('racing', 'VBG'), ('broom', 'NN'), ('Look', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('new', 'JJ'), ('Nimbus', 'NNP'), ('2000', 'CD'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('fastest', 'JJS'), ('model', 'NN'), ('yet', 'RB')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Look', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Look', 'NNP')])]",[Nimbus],"(S
  's/POS
  world/NN
  class/NN
  racing/VBG
  broom/NN
  (PERSON Look/NNP)
  's/POS
  new/JJ
  Nimbus/NNP
  2000/CD
  's/POS
  fastest/JJS
  model/NN
  yet/RB)"
142,6,2,1,"But, Hagrid, how am I to pay for all this? I haven't any money.","['Hagrid', 'pay', ""n't"", 'money']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('pay', 'VBP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('money', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],(S (GPE Hagrid/NNP) pay/VBP n't/RB money/NN)
143,6,2,5,"Well, there's your money, Harry.  Gringotts, the Wizard Bank. T'aint no place safer, 'cept perhaps Hogwarts.","['Well', ""'s"", 'money', 'Harry', 'Gringotts', 'Wizard', 'Bank', ""T'aint"", 'place', 'safer', ""'cept"", 'perhaps', 'Hogwarts']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Well', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('money', 'NN'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Gringotts', 'NNP'), ('Wizard', 'NNP'), ('Bank', 'NNP'), (""T'aint"", 'NNP'), ('place', 'NN'), ('safer', 'NN'), (""'cept"", 'IN'), ('perhaps', 'RB'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Well', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Gringotts', 'NNP'), ('Wizard', 'NNP'), ('Bank', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Well', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Gringotts', 'NNP'), ('Wizard', 'NNP'), ('Bank', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Gringotts, the Wizard Bank]","(S
  (PERSON Well/NNP)
  's/POS
  money/NN
  (PERSON Harry/NNP Gringotts/NNP Wizard/NNP Bank/NNP)
  T'aint/NNP
  place/NN
  safer/NN
  'cept/IN
  perhaps/RB
  Hogwarts/NNS)"
144,6,2,1,"Uh, Hagrid, what exactly are these things?","['Uh', 'Hagrid', 'exactly', 'things']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Uh', 'NNP'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('exactly', 'RB'), ('things', 'NNS')]",[],[],[Hagrid],(S Uh/NNP Hagrid/NNP exactly/RB things/NNS)
145,6,2,5,"They're goblins, Harry. Clever as they come goblins, but not the most friendly of beasts. Best stick close to me.  Mr. Harry Potter wishes to make a withdrawal.","[""'re"", 'goblins', 'Harry', 'Clever', 'come', 'goblins', 'friendly', 'beasts', 'Best', 'stick', 'close', 'Mr.', 'Harry', 'Potter', 'wishes', 'make', 'withdrawal']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'re"", 'VBP'), ('goblins', 'NNS'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Clever', 'NNP'), ('come', 'VBP'), ('goblins', 'NNS'), ('friendly', 'JJ'), ('beasts', 'NNS'), ('Best', 'NNP'), ('stick', 'NN'), ('close', 'RB'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('wishes', 'NNS'), ('make', 'VBP'), ('withdrawal', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Clever', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Clever', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Harry Potter]","(S
  're/VBP
  goblins/NNS
  (PERSON Harry/NNP Clever/NNP)
  come/VBP
  goblins/NNS
  friendly/JJ
  beasts/NNS
  Best/NNP
  stick/NN
  close/RB
  (PERSON Mr./NNP Harry/NNP)
  Potter/NNP
  wishes/NNS
  make/VBP
  withdrawal/NN)"
146,6,2,130,And does Mr. Harry Potter have his key?,"['Mr.', 'Harry', 'Potter', 'key']",Merpeople,,,"[('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('key', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]",[Harry Potter],(S (PERSON Mr./NNP) (PERSON Harry/NNP Potter/NNP) key/NN)
147,6,2,5,"Oh. Wait a minute. Got it here somewhere. Hah. There's the little devil.  Oh, and there's something else as well.  Professor Dumbledore gave me this.  It's about you-know-what in vault you-know-which.","['Oh', 'Wait', 'minute', 'Got', 'somewhere', 'Hah', ""'s"", 'little', 'devil', 'Oh', ""'s"", 'something', 'else', 'well', 'Professor', 'Dumbledore', 'gave', ""'s"", 'you-know-what', 'vault', 'you-know-which']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('Wait', 'NNP'), ('minute', 'NN'), ('Got', 'NNP'), ('somewhere', 'RB'), ('Hah', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('little', 'JJ'), ('devil', 'JJ'), ('Oh', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('something', 'NN'), ('else', 'RB'), ('well', 'RB'), ('Professor', 'NNP'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP'), ('gave', 'VBD'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('you-know-what', 'JJ'), ('vault', 'NN'), ('you-know-which', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Got', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hah', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Got', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hah', 'NNP')])]","[a minute, Dumbledore]","(S
  Oh/UH
  Wait/NNP
  minute/NN
  (PERSON Got/NNP)
  somewhere/RB
  (PERSON Hah/NNP)
  's/POS
  little/JJ
  devil/JJ
  Oh/NNP
  's/POS
  something/NN
  else/RB
  well/RB
  Professor/NNP
  Dumbledore/NNP
  gave/VBD
  's/POS
  you-know-what/JJ
  vault/NN
  you-know-which/JJ)"
148,6,2,130,Very well.,['well'],Merpeople,,,"[('well', 'RB')]",[],[],[],(S well/RB)
149,6,2,30,"Vault 687. Lamp, please.  Key please.","['Vault', '687', 'Lamp', 'please', 'Key', 'please']",Griphook,Male,,"[('Vault', 'NNP'), ('687', 'CD'), ('Lamp', 'NNP'), ('please', 'NN'), ('Key', 'NNP'), ('please', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Key', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Key', 'NNP')])]",[Vault 687],(S Vault/NNP 687/CD Lamp/NNP please/NN (PERSON Key/NNP) please/NN)
150,6,2,5,"Didn't think your mum and dad would leave you with nothing now, did ya?","[""n't"", 'think', 'mum', 'dad', 'would', 'leave', 'nothing', 'ya']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""n't"", 'RB'), ('think', 'VB'), ('mum', 'JJ'), ('dad', 'NN'), ('would', 'MD'), ('leave', 'VB'), ('nothing', 'NN'), ('ya', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S n't/RB think/VB mum/JJ dad/NN would/MD leave/VB nothing/NN ya/NN)
151,6,2,30,Vault 713.,"['Vault', '713']",Griphook,Male,,"[('Vault', 'NN'), ('713', 'CD')]",[],[],[Vault 713],(S Vault/NN 713/CD)
152,6,2,1,"What's in there, Hagrid?","[""'s"", 'Hagrid']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],(S 's/POS (PERSON Hagrid/NNP))
153,6,2,5,"Can't tell you, Harry. It's Hogwarts business. Very secret.","['Ca', ""n't"", 'tell', 'Harry', ""'s"", 'Hogwarts', 'business', 'secret']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Ca', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('tell', 'VB'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('business', 'NN'), ('secret', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],"(S
  Ca/NNP
  n't/RB
  tell/VB
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  's/POS
  (ORGANIZATION Hogwarts/NNP)
  business/NN
  secret/NN)"
154,6,2,30,Stand back.,"['Stand', 'back']",Griphook,Male,,"[('Stand', 'NNP'), ('back', 'RB')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Stand', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (GPE Stand/NNP) back/RB)
155,6,2,5,"Best not mention this to anyone, Harry.","['Best', 'mention', 'anyone', 'Harry']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Best', 'JJS'), ('mention', 'NN'), ('anyone', 'NN'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S Best/JJS mention/NN anyone/NN (PERSON Harry/NNP))
156,7,4,1,I still need...a wand.,"['still', 'need', '...', 'wand']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('still', 'RB'), ('need', 'VB'), ('...', ':'), ('wand', 'VB')]",[],[],[],(S still/RB need/VB .../: wand/VB)
157,7,4,5,"A wand? Well, you'll want Ollivanders.  No place better. Run along there, but wait. I just got one more thing I got to do. Won't be long.","['wand', 'Well', ""'ll"", 'want', 'Ollivanders', 'place', 'better', 'Run', 'along', 'wait', 'got', 'one', 'thing', 'got', 'Wo', ""n't"", 'long']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('wand', 'RB'), ('Well', 'NNP'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('want', 'VB'), ('Ollivanders', 'NNP'), ('place', 'NN'), ('better', 'RBR'), ('Run', 'NNP'), ('along', 'RB'), ('wait', 'VBD'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('one', 'CD'), ('thing', 'NN'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('Wo', 'NNP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('long', 'RB')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Ollivanders', 'NNP')])]","[Ollivanders, one]","(S
  wand/RB
  Well/NNP
  'll/MD
  want/VB
  (GPE Ollivanders/NNP)
  place/NN
  better/RBR
  Run/NNP
  along/RB
  wait/VBD
  got/VBD
  one/CD
  thing/NN
  got/VBD
  Wo/NNP
  n't/RB
  long/RB)"
158,7,4,1,Hello? Hello?,"['Hello', 'Hello']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Hello', 'NNP'), ('Hello', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hello', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hello', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Hello', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Hello/NNP) (ORGANIZATION Hello/NNP))
159,7,4,43,"I wondered when I'd be seeing you, Mr. Potter. It seems only yesterday that your mother and father were in here buying their first wands.  Ah. Here we are.  Well, give it a wave.  Apparently not.  Perhaps this.  No, no, definitely not! No matter...  I wonder.  Curious, very curious.","['wondered', ""'d"", 'seeing', 'Mr.', 'Potter', 'seems', 'yesterday', 'mother', 'father', 'buying', 'first', 'wands', 'Ah', 'Well', 'give', 'wave', 'Apparently', 'Perhaps', 'definitely', 'matter', '...', 'wonder', 'Curious', 'curious']",Garrick Ollivander,Male,Ravenclaw,"[('wondered', 'VBN'), (""'d"", 'MD'), ('seeing', 'VBG'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('seems', 'VBZ'), ('yesterday', 'NN'), ('mother', 'NN'), ('father', 'NN'), ('buying', 'NN'), ('first', 'JJ'), ('wands', 'VBZ'), ('Ah', 'NNP'), ('Well', 'NNP'), ('give', 'VB'), ('wave', 'NN'), ('Apparently', 'NNP'), ('Perhaps', 'RB'), ('definitely', 'RB'), ('matter', 'NN'), ('...', ':'), ('wonder', 'VBP'), ('Curious', 'NNP'), ('curious', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Ah', 'NNP'), ('Well', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Curious', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Ah', 'NNP'), ('Well', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Curious', 'NNP')])]","[Potter, first]","(S
  wondered/VBN
  'd/MD
  seeing/VBG
  (PERSON Mr./NNP Potter/NNP)
  seems/VBZ
  yesterday/NN
  mother/NN
  father/NN
  buying/NN
  first/JJ
  wands/VBZ
  (PERSON Ah/NNP Well/NNP)
  give/VB
  wave/NN
  Apparently/NNP
  Perhaps/RB
  definitely/RB
  matter/NN
  .../:
  wonder/VBP
  (PERSON Curious/NNP)
  curious/JJ)"
160,7,4,1,"Sorry, but what's curious?","['Sorry', ""'s"", 'curious']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Sorry', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('curious', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Sorry/NNP) 's/POS curious/JJ)
161,7,4,43,"I remember every wand I've ever sold, Mr. Potter. It just so happens that the phoenix, whose tail feather resides in your wand gave one other feather, just one. It is curious that you should be destined for this wand when its brother gave you that scar.","['remember', 'every', 'wand', ""'ve"", 'ever', 'sold', 'Mr.', 'Potter', 'happens', 'phoenix', 'whose', 'tail', 'feather', 'resides', 'wand', 'gave', 'one', 'feather', 'one', 'curious', 'destined', 'wand', 'brother', 'gave', 'scar']",Garrick Ollivander,Male,Ravenclaw,"[('remember', 'VB'), ('every', 'DT'), ('wand', 'NN'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('ever', 'RB'), ('sold', 'VBN'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), ('happens', 'VBZ'), ('phoenix', 'NN'), ('whose', 'WP$'), ('tail', 'NN'), ('feather', 'NN'), ('resides', 'NNS'), ('wand', 'VBP'), ('gave', 'VBD'), ('one', 'CD'), ('feather', 'NN'), ('one', 'CD'), ('curious', 'JJ'), ('destined', 'VBN'), ('wand', 'NN'), ('brother', 'NN'), ('gave', 'VBD'), ('scar', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Potter, one]","(S
  remember/VB
  every/DT
  wand/NN
  've/VBP
  ever/RB
  sold/VBN
  (PERSON Mr./NNP Potter/NNP)
  happens/VBZ
  phoenix/NN
  whose/WP$
  tail/NN
  feather/NN
  resides/NNS
  wand/VBP
  gave/VBD
  one/CD
  feather/NN
  one/CD
  curious/JJ
  destined/VBN
  wand/NN
  brother/NN
  gave/VBD
  scar/NN)"
162,7,4,1,And...who owned that wand?,"['...', 'owned', 'wand']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('...', ':'), ('owned', 'VBD'), ('wand', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S .../: owned/VBD wand/NN)
163,7,4,43,"Oh, we do not speak his name. The wand chooses the wizard, Mr. Potter. It's not always clear why, but I think it is clear that we can expect great things from you. After all, He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named did great things...terrible, yes, but great.","['Oh', 'speak', 'name', 'wand', 'chooses', 'wizard', 'Mr.', 'Potter', ""'s"", 'always', 'clear', 'think', 'clear', 'expect', 'great', 'things', 'He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named', 'great', 'things', '...', 'terrible', 'yes', 'great']",Garrick Ollivander,Male,Ravenclaw,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('speak', 'NN'), ('name', 'NN'), ('wand', 'VBP'), ('chooses', 'VBZ'), ('wizard', 'IN'), ('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('always', 'RB'), ('clear', 'JJ'), ('think', 'VBP'), ('clear', 'JJ'), ('expect', 'VBP'), ('great', 'JJ'), ('things', 'NNS'), ('He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named', 'NNP'), ('great', 'JJ'), ('things', 'NNS'), ('...', ':'), ('terrible', 'JJ'), ('yes', 'NNS'), ('great', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Mr.', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]",[Potter],"(S
  Oh/UH
  speak/NN
  name/NN
  wand/VBP
  chooses/VBZ
  wizard/IN
  (PERSON Mr./NNP Potter/NNP)
  's/POS
  always/RB
  clear/JJ
  think/VBP
  clear/JJ
  expect/VBP
  great/JJ
  things/NNS
  He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named/NNP
  great/JJ
  things/NNS
  .../:
  terrible/JJ
  yes/NNS
  great/JJ)"
164,7,4,5,Harry! Harry! Happy birthday!,"['Harry', 'Harry', 'Happy', 'birthday']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Happy', 'NNP'), ('birthday', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Happy', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Happy', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S (PERSON Harry/NNP) (PERSON Harry/NNP Happy/NNP) birthday/NN)
165,7,4,1,Wow.,['Wow'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Wow', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Wow', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Wow/NN))
166,8,5,5,"You all right, Harry? You seem very quiet.","['right', 'Harry', 'seem', 'quiet']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('right', 'JJ'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('seem', 'VBP'), ('quiet', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],(S right/JJ (PERSON Harry/NNP) seem/VBP quiet/JJ)
167,8,5,1,"He killed my parents, didn't he? The one who gave me this. You know, Hagrid, I know you do.","['killed', 'parents', ""n't"", 'one', 'gave', 'know', 'Hagrid', 'know']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('killed', 'VBN'), ('parents', 'NNS'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('one', 'CD'), ('gave', 'VBD'), ('know', 'VBN'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('know', 'VBP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]",[Hagrid],"(S
  killed/VBN
  parents/NNS
  n't/RB
  one/CD
  gave/VBD
  know/VBN
  (PERSON Hagrid/NNP)
  know/VBP)"
168,8,5,5,"First, and understand this, Harry, 'cause it's very important. Not all wizards are good. Some of them go bad. A few years ago, there was one wizard who went as bad as you can go. And his name was V-...his name was V-...","['First', 'understand', 'Harry', ""'cause"", ""'s"", 'important', 'wizards', 'good', 'go', 'bad', 'years', 'ago', 'one', 'wizard', 'went', 'bad', 'go', 'name', 'V-', '...', 'name', 'V-', '...']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('First', 'NNP'), ('understand', 'NN'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'cause"", 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('important', 'JJ'), ('wizards', 'NNS'), ('good', 'JJ'), ('go', 'VBP'), ('bad', 'JJ'), ('years', 'NNS'), ('ago', 'IN'), ('one', 'CD'), ('wizard', 'WDT'), ('went', 'VBD'), ('bad', 'JJ'), ('go', 'VB'), ('name', 'JJ'), ('V-', 'NNP'), ('...', ':'), ('name', 'NN'), ('V-', 'NNP'), ('...', ':')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'cause"", 'NNP')])]","[Tree('GPE', [('First', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'cause"", 'NNP')])]","[First, Harry, A few years ago, one]","(S
  (GPE First/NNP)
  understand/NN
  (PERSON Harry/NNP 'cause/NNP)
  's/POS
  important/JJ
  wizards/NNS
  good/JJ
  go/VBP
  bad/JJ
  years/NNS
  ago/IN
  one/CD
  wizard/WDT
  went/VBD
  bad/JJ
  go/VB
  name/JJ
  V-/NNP
  .../:
  name/NN
  V-/NNP
  .../:)"
169,8,5,1,Maybe if you wrote it down?,"['Maybe', 'wrote']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Maybe', 'RB'), ('wrote', 'VBD')]",[],[],[],(S Maybe/RB wrote/VBD)
170,8,5,5,"No, I can't spell it. All right.  Voldemort.","['ca', ""n't"", 'spell', 'right', 'Voldemort']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('ca', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('spell', 'VB'), ('right', 'JJ'), ('Voldemort', 'NNP')]",[],[],[Voldemort],(S ca/MD n't/RB spell/VB right/JJ Voldemort/NNP)
171,8,5,1,Voldemort?,['Voldemort'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Voldemort', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Voldemort', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Voldemort/NN))
172,8,5,5,Shh!!,['Shh'],Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Shh', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Shh', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Shh/NN))
173,8,5,5,"It was dark times, Harry, dark times.  Voldemort started to gather some followers, brought 'em over to the dark side. Anyone that stood up to him ended up dead. Your parents fought against him, but nobody lived once he decided to kill 'em.  Nobody...not one. Except you.","['dark', 'times', 'Harry', 'dark', 'times', 'Voldemort', 'started', 'gather', 'followers', 'brought', ""'em"", 'dark', 'side', 'Anyone', 'stood', 'ended', 'dead', 'parents', 'fought', 'nobody', 'lived', 'decided', 'kill', ""'em"", 'Nobody', '...', 'one', 'Except']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('dark', 'JJ'), ('times', 'NNS'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('dark', 'NN'), ('times', 'NNS'), ('Voldemort', 'NNP'), ('started', 'VBD'), ('gather', 'JJR'), ('followers', 'NNS'), ('brought', 'VBD'), (""'em"", 'PRP'), ('dark', 'JJ'), ('side', 'NN'), ('Anyone', 'NNP'), ('stood', 'VBD'), ('ended', 'VBN'), ('dead', 'JJ'), ('parents', 'NNS'), ('fought', 'VBN'), ('nobody', 'NN'), ('lived', 'VBD'), ('decided', 'VBD'), ('kill', 'NN'), (""'em"", 'PRP'), ('Nobody', 'NN'), ('...', ':'), ('one', 'CD'), ('Except', 'IN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Voldemort', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Anyone', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Voldemort', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Anyone', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Voldemort]","(S
  dark/JJ
  times/NNS
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  dark/NN
  times/NNS
  (PERSON Voldemort/NNP)
  started/VBD
  gather/JJR
  followers/NNS
  brought/VBD
  'em/PRP
  dark/JJ
  side/NN
  (PERSON Anyone/NNP)
  stood/VBD
  ended/VBN
  dead/JJ
  parents/NNS
  fought/VBN
  nobody/NN
  lived/VBD
  decided/VBD
  kill/NN
  'em/PRP
  Nobody/NN
  .../:
  one/CD
  Except/IN)"
174,8,5,1,Me? Voldemort tried to kill...me?,"['Voldemort', 'tried', 'kill', '...']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Voldemort', 'NNP'), ('tried', 'VBD'), ('kill', 'NN'), ('...', ':')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Voldemort', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Voldemort', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Voldemort/NNP) tried/VBD kill/NN .../:)
175,8,5,5,"Yes. That ain't no ordinary cut on your forehead, Harry. A mark like that only comes from being touched by a curse...and an evil curse at that.","['Yes', 'ai', ""n't"", 'ordinary', 'cut', 'forehead', 'Harry', 'mark', 'like', 'comes', 'touched', 'curse', '...', 'evil', 'curse']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Yes', 'UH'), ('ai', 'VBP'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('ordinary', 'JJ'), ('cut', 'VBN'), ('forehead', 'JJ'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('mark', 'NN'), ('like', 'IN'), ('comes', 'VBZ'), ('touched', 'JJ'), ('curse', 'NN'), ('...', ':'), ('evil', 'JJ'), ('curse', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP')])]",[Harry],"(S
  Yes/UH
  ai/VBP
  n't/RB
  ordinary/JJ
  cut/VBN
  forehead/JJ
  (PERSON Harry/NNP)
  mark/NN
  like/IN
  comes/VBZ
  touched/JJ
  curse/NN
  .../:
  evil/JJ
  curse/NN)"
176,8,5,1,What happened to...to You-Know-Who?,"['happened', '...', 'You-Know-Who']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('happened', 'VBD'), ('...', ':'), ('You-Know-Who', 'JJ')]",[],[],[],(S happened/VBD .../: You-Know-Who/JJ)
177,8,5,5,"Well, some say he died. Codswallop in my opinion. Nope, I reckon he's out there, still, too tired to go on. But one thing's absolutely certain. Something about you stumped him that night. That's why you're famous. That's why everybody knows your name. You're the boy who lived.","['Well', 'say', 'died', 'Codswallop', 'opinion', 'Nope', 'reckon', ""'s"", 'still', 'tired', 'go', 'one', 'thing', ""'s"", 'absolutely', 'certain', 'Something', 'stumped', 'night', ""'s"", ""'re"", 'famous', ""'s"", 'everybody', 'knows', 'name', ""'re"", 'boy', 'lived']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Well', 'RB'), ('say', 'VB'), ('died', 'VBD'), ('Codswallop', 'NNP'), ('opinion', 'NN'), ('Nope', 'NNP'), ('reckon', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('still', 'RB'), ('tired', 'VBN'), ('go', 'VBP'), ('one', 'CD'), ('thing', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('absolutely', 'RB'), ('certain', 'JJ'), ('Something', 'NNP'), ('stumped', 'VBD'), ('night', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('famous', 'JJ'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('everybody', 'NN'), ('knows', 'VBZ'), ('name', 'NN'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('boy', 'NN'), ('lived', 'VBD')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Codswallop', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Nope', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Codswallop', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Nope', 'NNP')])]",[one],"(S
  Well/RB
  say/VB
  died/VBD
  (PERSON Codswallop/NNP)
  opinion/NN
  (PERSON Nope/NNP)
  reckon/NN
  's/POS
  still/RB
  tired/VBN
  go/VBP
  one/CD
  thing/NN
  's/POS
  absolutely/RB
  certain/JJ
  Something/NNP
  stumped/VBD
  night/NN
  's/POS
  're/VBP
  famous/JJ
  's/POS
  everybody/NN
  knows/VBZ
  name/NN
  're/VBP
  boy/NN
  lived/VBD)"
178,9,71,5,"What're you looking at?  Blimey, is that the time? Sorry, Harry, I'm gonna have to leave you. Dumbledore'll be wanting his- well, he'll be wanting to see me. Now, uh, your train leaves in 10 minutes. Here's your ticket.  Stick to it, Harry that's very important. Stick to your ticket.","[""'re"", 'looking', 'Blimey', 'time', 'Sorry', 'Harry', ""'m"", 'gon', 'na', 'leave', 'Dumbledore', ""'ll"", 'wanting', 'his-', 'well', ""'ll"", 'wanting', 'see', 'uh', 'train', 'leaves', '10', 'minutes', ""'s"", 'ticket', 'Stick', 'Harry', ""'s"", 'important', 'Stick', 'ticket']",Rubeus Hagrid,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'re"", 'VBP'), ('looking', 'VBG'), ('Blimey', 'NNP'), ('time', 'NN'), ('Sorry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('gon', 'VBG'), ('na', 'TO'), ('leave', 'VB'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('wanting', 'VBG'), ('his-', 'RB'), ('well', 'RB'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('wanting', 'VBG'), ('see', 'VB'), ('uh', 'JJ'), ('train', 'NN'), ('leaves', 'VBZ'), ('10', 'CD'), ('minutes', 'NNS'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('ticket', 'NN'), ('Stick', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('important', 'JJ'), ('Stick', 'NNP'), ('ticket', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Blimey', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Dumbledore', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Stick', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Blimey', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Dumbledore', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Stick', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP')])]","[Blimey, Harry, 10 minutes, Stick, Harry]","(S
  're/VBP
  looking/VBG
  (PERSON Blimey/NNP)
  time/NN
  (PERSON Sorry/NNP Harry/NNP)
  'm/VBP
  gon/VBG
  na/TO
  leave/VB
  (PERSON Dumbledore/NNP)
  'll/MD
  wanting/VBG
  his-/RB
  well/RB
  'll/MD
  wanting/VBG
  see/VB
  uh/JJ
  train/NN
  leaves/VBZ
  10/CD
  minutes/NNS
  's/POS
  ticket/NN
  (PERSON Stick/NNP Harry/NNP)
  's/POS
  important/JJ
  Stick/NNP
  ticket/NN)"
179,9,71,1,"Platform 9&? But, Hagrid, there must be a mistake. This says Platform 9&. There's no such thing...is there?","['Platform', '9', '', 'Hagrid', 'must', 'mistake', 'says', 'Platform', '9', '', ""'s"", 'thing', '...']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Platform', 'VB'), ('9', 'CD'), ('', 'JJ'), ('Hagrid', 'NNP'), ('must', 'MD'), ('mistake', 'VB'), ('says', 'VBZ'), ('Platform', 'NNP'), ('9', 'CD'), ('', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('thing', 'NN'), ('...', ':')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hagrid', 'NNP')])]","[Hagrid, Platform 9&.]","(S
  Platform/VB
  9/CD
  /JJ
  (PERSON Hagrid/NNP)
  must/MD
  mistake/VB
  says/VBZ
  Platform/NNP
  9/CD
  /NNP
  's/POS
  thing/NN
  .../:)"
180,9,71,139,Sorry.,['Sorry'],Man,,,"[('Sorry', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NN')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Sorry', 'NN')])]",[],(S (PERSON Sorry/NN))
181,9,71,1,"Excuse me, excuse me.","['Excuse', 'excuse']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Excuse', 'NN'), ('excuse', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Excuse', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Excuse/NN) excuse/NN)
182,9,71,149,"Right on your left, ma'am.","['Right', 'left', ""ma'am""]",Old man,,,"[('Right', 'RB'), ('left', 'VBD'), (""ma'am"", 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S Right/RB left/VBD ma'am/NN)
183,9,71,1,"Excuse me, sir. Can you tell me where I might find Platform 9&?","['Excuse', 'sir', 'tell', 'might', 'find', 'Platform', '9', '']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Excuse', 'NNP'), ('sir', 'NN'), ('tell', 'NN'), ('might', 'MD'), ('find', 'VB'), ('Platform', 'NNP'), ('9', 'CD'), ('', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Excuse', 'NNP')])]",[Platform 9&],"(S
  (GPE Excuse/NNP)
  sir/NN
  tell/NN
  might/MD
  find/VB
  Platform/NNP
  9/CD
  /NN)"
184,9,71,149,"9&? Think you're being funny, do ya?","['9', '', 'Think', ""'re"", 'funny', 'ya']",Old man,,,"[('9', 'CD'), ('', 'JJ'), ('Think', 'NNP'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('funny', 'JJ'), ('ya', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S 9/CD /JJ Think/NNP 're/VBP funny/JJ ya/NN)
185,9,71,26,"It's the same year after year. Always packed with Muggles, of course.","[""'s"", 'year', 'year', 'Always', 'packed', 'Muggles', 'course']",Molly Weasley,Female,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('year', 'NN'), ('year', 'NN'), ('Always', 'NNP'), ('packed', 'VBD'), ('Muggles', 'NNP'), ('course', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Always', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Muggles', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Always', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Muggles', 'NNP')])]",[the same year after year],"(S
  's/POS
  year/NN
  year/NN
  (PERSON Always/NNP)
  packed/VBD
  (PERSON Muggles/NNP)
  course/NN)"
186,9,71,1,Muggles?,['Muggles'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Muggles', 'NNS')]",[],[],[],(S Muggles/NNS)
187,9,71,26,"Come on. Platform 9& this way! All right, Percy, you first.","['Come', 'Platform', '9', '', 'way', 'right', 'Percy', 'first']",Molly Weasley,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Come', 'NNP'), ('Platform', 'NNP'), ('9', 'CD'), ('', 'NNP'), ('way', 'NN'), ('right', 'RB'), ('Percy', 'NNP'), ('first', 'RB')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Percy', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Percy', 'NNP')])]","[Percy, first]","(S
  Come/NNP
  Platform/NNP
  9/CD
  /NNP
  way/NN
  right/RB
  (PERSON Percy/NNP)
  first/RB)"
188,9,71,26,"Fred, you next.","['Fred', 'next']",Molly Weasley,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Fred', 'NNP'), ('next', 'JJ')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Fred', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (GPE Fred/NNP) next/JJ)
189,9,71,19,"He's not Fred, I am!","[""'s"", 'Fred']",George Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('Fred', 'NNP')]",[],[],[Fred],(S 's/POS Fred/NNP)
190,9,71,14,"Honestly, woman, you call yourself our mother.","['Honestly', 'woman', 'call', 'mother']",Fred Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Honestly', 'RB'), ('woman', 'NN'), ('call', 'NN'), ('mother', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S Honestly/RB woman/NN call/NN mother/NN)
191,9,71,26,"Oh, I'm sorry, George.","['Oh', ""'m"", 'sorry', 'George']",Molly Weasley,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'UH'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('sorry', 'JJ'), ('George', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('George', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('George', 'NNP')])]",[George],(S Oh/UH 'm/VBP sorry/JJ (PERSON George/NNP))
192,9,71,14,I'm only joking. I am Fred.,"[""'m"", 'joking', 'Fred']",Fred Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'m"", 'VBP'), ('joking', 'VBG'), ('Fred', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Fred', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Fred', 'NNP')])]",[Fred],(S 'm/VBP joking/VBG (PERSON Fred/NNP))
193,9,71,1,Excuse me! C-could you tell me how to-,"['Excuse', 'C-could', 'tell', 'to-']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Excuse', 'NNP'), ('C-could', 'NNP'), ('tell', 'NN'), ('to-', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Excuse', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Excuse', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Excuse/NNP) C-could/NNP tell/NN to-/NN)
194,9,71,26,"How to get on the platform? Yes, not to worry, dear. It's Ron's first time to Hogwarts as well.  Now, all you've got to do is walk straight at the wall between platforms 9 and 10. Best do it at a bit of a run if you're nervous.","['get', 'platform', 'Yes', 'worry', 'dear', ""'s"", 'Ron', ""'s"", 'first', 'time', 'Hogwarts', 'well', ""'ve"", 'got', 'walk', 'straight', 'wall', 'platforms', '9', '10', 'Best', 'bit', 'run', ""'re"", 'nervous']",Molly Weasley,Female,Gryffindor,"[('get', 'VB'), ('platform', 'JJ'), ('Yes', 'NNP'), ('worry', 'VBP'), ('dear', 'VBP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('Ron', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('first', 'JJ'), ('time', 'NN'), ('Hogwarts', 'NNP'), ('well', 'RB'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('got', 'VBN'), ('walk', 'VBP'), ('straight', 'RB'), ('wall', 'RB'), ('platforms', 'VBZ'), ('9', 'CD'), ('10', 'CD'), ('Best', 'NNP'), ('bit', 'NN'), ('run', 'VBP'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('nervous', 'JJ')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hogwarts', 'NNP')])]","[Ron, first, Hogwarts, 9, 10]","(S
  get/VB
  platform/JJ
  Yes/NNP
  worry/VBP
  dear/VBP
  's/POS
  (PERSON Ron/NNP)
  's/POS
  first/JJ
  time/NN
  (PERSON Hogwarts/NNP)
  well/RB
  've/VBP
  got/VBN
  walk/VBP
  straight/RB
  wall/RB
  platforms/VBZ
  9/CD
  10/CD
  Best/NNP
  bit/NN
  run/VBP
  're/VBP
  nervous/JJ)"
195,9,71,20,Good luck.,"['Good', 'luck']",Ginny Weasley,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Good', 'JJ'), ('luck', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Good', 'JJ')])]",[],(S (GPE Good/JJ) luck/NN)
196,10,42,2,"Excuse me, do you mind? Everywhere else is full.","['Excuse', 'mind', 'Everywhere', 'else', 'full']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Excuse', 'NNP'), ('mind', 'NN'), ('Everywhere', 'NNP'), ('else', 'RB'), ('full', 'JJ')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Excuse', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (GPE Excuse/NNP) mind/NN Everywhere/NNP else/RB full/JJ)
197,10,42,1,"No, not at all.",[],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,[],[],[],[],(S )
198,10,42,2,"I'm Ron, by the way. Ron Weasley.","[""'m"", 'Ron', 'way', 'Ron', 'Weasley']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'m"", 'VBP'), ('Ron', 'NNP'), ('way', 'NN'), ('Ron', 'NNP'), ('Weasley', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP'), ('Weasley', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP'), ('Weasley', 'NNP')])]","[Ron, Ron Weasley]",(S 'm/VBP (PERSON Ron/NNP) way/NN (PERSON Ron/NNP Weasley/NNP))
199,10,42,1,I'm Harry. Harry Potter.,"[""'m"", 'Harry', 'Harry', 'Potter']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'m"", 'VBP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')])]","[Harry, Harry Potter]",(S 'm/VBP (PERSON Harry/NNP Harry/NNP Potter/NNP))
200,10,42,2,"So-so it's true? I mean, do you really have the...the...","['So-so', ""'s"", 'true', 'mean', 'really', '...', '...']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('So-so', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('true', 'JJ'), ('mean', 'NN'), ('really', 'RB'), ('...', ':'), ('...', ':')]",[],[],[],(S So-so/NNP 's/POS true/JJ mean/NN really/RB .../: .../:)
201,10,42,1,The what?,[],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,[],[],[],[],(S )
202,10,42,2,Scar...?,"['Scar', '...']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Scar', 'NN'), ('...', ':')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Scar', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Scar/NN) .../:)
203,10,42,1,Oh,['Oh'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'UH')]",[],[],[],(S Oh/UH)
204,10,42,2,Wicked.,['Wicked'],Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Wicked', 'VBD')]",[],[],[],(S Wicked/VBD)
205,10,42,140,"Anything off the trolley, dears?","['Anything', 'trolley', 'dears']",Woman,,,"[('Anything', 'VBG'), ('trolley', 'JJ'), ('dears', 'NNS')]",[],[],[],(S Anything/VBG trolley/JJ dears/NNS)
206,10,42,2,"No, thanks, I'm all set.","['thanks', ""'m"", 'set']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('thanks', 'NNS'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('set', 'VBN')]",[],[],[],(S thanks/NNS 'm/VBP set/VBN)
207,10,42,1,We'll take the lot!,"[""'ll"", 'take', 'lot']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'ll"", 'MD'), ('take', 'VB'), ('lot', 'NN')]",[],[],[],(S 'll/MD take/VB lot/NN)
208,10,42,2,Whoa!,['Whoa'],Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Whoa', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Whoa', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Whoa/NN))
209,10,42,1,Bertie Bott's Every Flavour Beans?,"['Bertie', 'Bott', ""'s"", 'Every', 'Flavour', 'Beans']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Bertie', 'NNP'), ('Bott', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('Every', 'NNP'), ('Flavour', 'CD'), ('Beans', 'NNS')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Bertie', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Bertie', 'NNP')]), Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Bott', 'NNP')])]",[Bertie Bott's],"(S
  (PERSON Bertie/NNP)
  (ORGANIZATION Bott/NNP)
  's/POS
  Every/NNP
  Flavour/CD
  Beans/NNS)"
210,10,42,2,"They mean every flavour! There's chocolate and peppermint, and there's also spinach, liver and tripe. George sweared he got a bogey-flavoured one once!","['mean', 'every', 'flavour', ""'s"", 'chocolate', 'peppermint', ""'s"", 'also', 'spinach', 'liver', 'tripe', 'George', 'sweared', 'got', 'bogey-flavoured', 'one']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('mean', 'JJ'), ('every', 'DT'), ('flavour', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('chocolate', 'NN'), ('peppermint', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('also', 'RB'), ('spinach', 'VBP'), ('liver', 'RB'), ('tripe', 'JJ'), ('George', 'NNP'), ('sweared', 'VBD'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('bogey-flavoured', 'JJ'), ('one', 'CD')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('George', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('George', 'NNP')])]","[George, one]","(S
  mean/JJ
  every/DT
  flavour/NN
  's/POS
  chocolate/NN
  peppermint/NN
  's/POS
  also/RB
  spinach/VBP
  liver/RB
  tripe/JJ
  (PERSON George/NNP)
  sweared/VBD
  got/VBD
  bogey-flavoured/JJ
  one/CD)"
211,10,42,1,"These aren't real chocolate frogs, are they?","[""n't"", 'real', 'chocolate', 'frogs']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""n't"", 'RB'), ('real', 'JJ'), ('chocolate', 'VB'), ('frogs', 'NNS')]",[],[],[],(S n't/RB real/JJ chocolate/VB frogs/NNS)
212,10,42,2,"It's just a spell. Besides, it's the cards you want. Each pack's got a famous witch or wizard. I got about 500 meself.  Watch it!  Oh, that's rotten luck. They've only got one good jump in them to begin with.","[""'s"", 'spell', 'Besides', ""'s"", 'cards', 'want', 'pack', ""'s"", 'got', 'famous', 'witch', 'wizard', 'got', '500', 'meself', 'Watch', 'Oh', ""'s"", 'rotten', 'luck', ""'ve"", 'got', 'one', 'good', 'jump', 'begin']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'s"", 'POS'), ('spell', 'NN'), ('Besides', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('cards', 'NNS'), ('want', 'VBP'), ('pack', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('famous', 'JJ'), ('witch', 'NN'), ('wizard', 'NN'), ('got', 'VBD'), ('500', 'CD'), ('meself', 'PRP'), ('Watch', 'NNP'), ('Oh', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('rotten', 'JJ'), ('luck', 'NN'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('got', 'VBN'), ('one', 'CD'), ('good', 'JJ'), ('jump', 'NN'), ('begin', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Besides', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Watch', 'NNP'), ('Oh', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Besides', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Watch', 'NNP'), ('Oh', 'NNP')])]","[about 500, one]","(S
  's/POS
  spell/NN
  (PERSON Besides/NNP)
  's/POS
  cards/NNS
  want/VBP
  pack/NN
  's/POS
  got/VBD
  famous/JJ
  witch/NN
  wizard/NN
  got/VBD
  500/CD
  meself/PRP
  (PERSON Watch/NNP Oh/NNP)
  's/POS
  rotten/JJ
  luck/NN
  've/VBP
  got/VBN
  one/CD
  good/JJ
  jump/NN
  begin/NN)"
213,10,42,1,I got Dumbledore!,"['got', 'Dumbledore']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('got', 'VBD'), ('Dumbledore', 'NNP')]",[],"[Tree('ORGANIZATION', [('Dumbledore', 'NNP')])]",[Dumbledore],(S got/VBD (ORGANIZATION Dumbledore/NNP))
214,10,42,2,I got about 6 of him.,"['got', '6']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('got', 'VBD'), ('6', 'CD')]",[],[],[about 6],(S got/VBD 6/CD)
215,10,42,1,"Hey, he's gone!","['Hey', ""'s"", 'gone']",Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Hey', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('gone', 'VBN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hey', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Hey', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Hey/NNP) 's/POS gone/VBN)
216,10,42,2,"Well, you can't expect him to hang around all day, can you?  This is Scabbers, by the way, pathetic, isn't he?","['Well', 'ca', ""n't"", 'expect', 'hang', 'around', 'day', 'Scabbers', 'way', 'pathetic', ""n't""]",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Well', 'NNP'), ('ca', 'MD'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('expect', 'VB'), ('hang', 'NN'), ('around', 'IN'), ('day', 'NN'), ('Scabbers', 'NNP'), ('way', 'NN'), ('pathetic', 'JJ'), (""n't"", 'RB')]",[],[],[],"(S
  Well/NNP
  ca/MD
  n't/RB
  expect/VB
  hang/NN
  around/IN
  day/NN
  Scabbers/NNP
  way/NN
  pathetic/JJ
  n't/RB)"
217,10,42,1,A little.,['little'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('little', 'JJ')]",[],[],[],(S little/JJ)
218,10,42,2,Fred gave me a spell as to turn him yellow. Want to see?,"['Fred', 'gave', 'spell', 'turn', 'yellow', 'Want', 'see']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Fred', 'NNP'), ('gave', 'VBD'), ('spell', 'NN'), ('turn', 'NN'), ('yellow', 'JJ'), ('Want', 'NNP'), ('see', 'NN')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Fred', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Fred', 'NNP')])]",[],"(S
  (PERSON Fred/NNP)
  gave/VBD
  spell/NN
  turn/NN
  yellow/JJ
  Want/NNP
  see/NN)"
219,10,42,1,Yeah!,['Yeah'],Harry Potter,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Yeah', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Yeah', 'NN')])]",[],(S (GPE Yeah/NN))
220,10,42,2,Ahem. Sun-,"['Ahem', 'Sun-']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Ahem', 'NNP'), ('Sun-', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ahem', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ahem', 'NNP')])]",[],(S (PERSON Ahem/NNP) Sun-/NNP)
221,10,42,3,Has anyone seen a toad? A boy named Neville's lost one.,"['anyone', 'seen', 'toad', 'boy', 'named', 'Neville', ""'s"", 'lost', 'one']",Hermione Granger,Female,Gryffindor,"[('anyone', 'NN'), ('seen', 'VBN'), ('toad', 'NN'), ('boy', 'NN'), ('named', 'VBN'), ('Neville', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('lost', 'JJS'), ('one', 'CD')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Neville', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Neville', 'NNP')])]",[Neville],"(S
  anyone/NN
  seen/VBN
  toad/NN
  boy/NN
  named/VBN
  (PERSON Neville/NNP)
  's/POS
  lost/JJS
  one/CD)"
222,10,42,2,No.,[],Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,[],[],[],[],(S )
223,10,42,3,"Oh, are you doing magic? Let's see then.","['Oh', 'magic', 'Let', ""'s"", 'see']",Hermione Granger,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Oh', 'UH'), ('magic', 'JJ'), ('Let', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('see', 'VB')]",[],[],[],(S Oh/UH magic/JJ Let/NNP 's/POS see/VB)
224,10,42,2,"Sunshine, daises, butter mellow, turn this stupid fat rat yellow!","['Sunshine', 'daises', 'butter', 'mellow', 'turn', 'stupid', 'fat', 'rat', 'yellow']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[('Sunshine', 'NNP'), ('daises', 'VBZ'), ('butter', 'RB'), ('mellow', 'JJ'), ('turn', 'NN'), ('stupid', 'JJ'), ('fat', 'JJ'), ('rat', 'NN'), ('yellow', 'NN')]",[],"[Tree('GPE', [('Sunshine', 'NNP')])]",[],"(S
  (GPE Sunshine/NNP)
  daises/VBZ
  butter/RB
  mellow/JJ
  turn/NN
  stupid/JJ
  fat/JJ
  rat/NN
  yellow/NN)"
225,10,42,3,"Are you sure that's a real spell? Well, it's not very good, is it? Of course I've only tried a few simple spells myself, and they've all worked for me. For example...  Oculus Reparo.  That's better, isn't it? Holy Cricket, you're Harry Potter. I'm Hermione Granger...and you are...?","['sure', ""'s"", 'real', 'spell', 'Well', ""'s"", 'good', 'course', ""'ve"", 'tried', 'simple', 'spells', ""'ve"", 'worked', 'example', '...', 'Oculus', 'Reparo', ""'s"", 'better', ""n't"", 'Holy', 'Cricket', ""'re"", 'Harry', 'Potter', ""'m"", 'Hermione', 'Granger', '...', '...']",Hermione Granger,Female,Gryffindor,"[('sure', 'NN'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('real', 'JJ'), ('spell', 'NN'), ('Well', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('good', 'JJ'), ('course', 'NN'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('tried', 'VBN'), ('simple', 'JJ'), ('spells', 'NNS'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('worked', 'VBN'), ('example', 'NN'), ('...', ':'), ('Oculus', 'CC'), ('Reparo', 'NNP'), (""'s"", 'POS'), ('better', 'JJR'), (""n't"", 'RB'), ('Holy', 'NNP'), ('Cricket', 'NNP'), (""'re"", 'VBP'), ('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP'), (""'m"", 'VBP'), ('Hermione', 'NNP'), ('Granger', 'NNP'), ('...', ':'), ('...', ':')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Well', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Reparo', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Holy', 'NNP'), ('Cricket', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hermione', 'NNP'), ('Granger', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Well', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Reparo', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Holy', 'NNP'), ('Cricket', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Harry', 'NNP'), ('Potter', 'NNP')]), Tree('PERSON', [('Hermione', 'NNP'), ('Granger', 'NNP')])]","[Oculus Reparo, Harry Potter, Hermione Granger]","(S
  sure/NN
  's/POS
  real/JJ
  spell/NN
  (PERSON Well/NNP)
  's/POS
  good/JJ
  course/NN
  've/VBP
  tried/VBN
  simple/JJ
  spells/NNS
  've/VBP
  worked/VBN
  example/NN
  .../:
  Oculus/CC
  (PERSON Reparo/NNP)
  's/POS
  better/JJR
  n't/RB
  (PERSON Holy/NNP Cricket/NNP)
  're/VBP
  (PERSON Harry/NNP Potter/NNP)
  'm/VBP
  (PERSON Hermione/NNP Granger/NNP)
  .../:
  .../:)"
226,10,42,2,I'm...Ron Weasley.,"[""'m"", '...', 'Ron', 'Weasley']",Ron Weasley,Male,Gryffindor,"[(""'m"", 'VBP'), ('...', ':'), ('Ron', 'NNP'), ('Weasley', 'NNP')]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP'), ('Weasley', 'NNP')])]","[Tree('PERSON', [('Ron', 'NNP'), ('Weasley', 'NNP')])]",[Ron Weasley],(S 'm/VBP .../: (PERSON Ron/NNP Weasley/NNP))
227,10,42,3,"Pleasure. You two better change into your robes. I expect we'll be arriving soon.  You've got dirt, on your nose, by the way, did you know? Just there.","['Pleasure', 'two', 'better', 'change', 'robes', 'expect', ""'ll"", 'arriving', 'soon', ""'ve"", 'got', 'dirt', 'nose', 'way', 'know']",Hermione Granger,Female,Gryffindor,"[('Pleasure', 'NN'), ('two', 'CD'), ('better', 'JJR'), ('change', 'NN'), ('robes', 'NNS'), ('expect', 'VBP'), (""'ll"", 'MD'), ('arriving', 'VBG'), ('soon', 'RB'), (""'ve"", 'VBP'), ('got', 'VBN'), ('dirt', 'NNS'), ('nose', 'JJ'), ('way', 'NN'), ('know', 'VBP')]",[],[],[two],"(S
  Pleasure/NN
  two/CD
  better/JJR
  change/NN
  robes/NNS
